Speaker 1: all right guys welcome in i have a lot to cover today we have hit a gold mine here of information that to me has changed quite
Speaker 2: a bit
uh of my
Speaker 1: impression of miss erica
Speaker 3: francefay and uh how she ended up in charlie kirk's life frankly i didn't want to oversell the show i didn't want people i did that one time i didn't mean to of course but i thought man
Speaker 4: this is a big show and then you know like the five people who didn't like it were like that wasn't a big show who you call it a big show, big show. That's a weak show.
i
Speaker 4: hate your show
so i i did i
Speaker 4: purposely didn't oversell it
Speaker 1: but uh welcome in welcome in we have a lot to cover today a
lot to cover we're a
Speaker 1: little early we're a little early i know that's going to confuse some people i figured with the
frankly candace
Speaker 5: opening right here in the middle of the day it might be nice to uh to let some of our european listeners in a little earlier let some of our australian listeners wake up to us
Speaker 1: just a shade earlier
um but
Speaker 1: this is not a show i think you're going to want to miss i think this opens up a whole new avenue of the investigation because as
we ask
Speaker 6: ourselves who killed charlie kirk how and why i
think there's a
Speaker 6: lot about the answer that
Speaker 7: depends on how did erica kirk end up in her in his life and what was she doing
before she got
Speaker 7: there what was she doing i i
Speaker 7: I didn't know there's this massive gap in a resume. We're going to cover some of it today
because
Speaker 8: now we have answers. Now we have answers of what she was doing in that crucial period of time. If you're watching Candace's show yesterday, I'll play a short clip of it today. If you're watching her show yesterday, she asked the same question. What was she doing in this time
Speaker 7: period?
She didn't
Speaker 7: know either. Luckily, I've got a Daisy in my back pocket and Daisy leaves
no
Speaker 8: stone unturned. If there's a question, she's going to find an answer. So welcome in.
Speaker 8: Welcome in.
Speaker 9: Bienvenidos, our friends south of the border, and we will get going here in mere moments. Oh, the opening is one of my absolute favorite topics. I forgot
to tell
Speaker 9: you that. The opening today is one of my absolute very favorite topics, and I intend to get to it with rapidity. It'll be fun. It'll be a lot
Speaker 5: of fun. It's got a South American connection. I don't want you to miss that while we're talking about...
Speaker 5: Um, the, I don't want you to miss that in the open because it has application to the actual show.
Speaker 8: It has application to where in the world was Erica Fransfey during
Speaker 6: 2017. I
found
Speaker 10: her. Well,
Daisy
Speaker 6: found her. I'll tell you where she was. Uh,
a lot of
Speaker 6: fun putting this show together. A
lot of
Speaker 6: fun putting the
Speaker 11: opening together.
And I
Speaker 11: hope you get as much out of it
as your
Speaker 11: humble host did. It's a lot of fun, a whole lot of fun.
So for
Speaker 11: those wondering where Candace is on this fine afternoon, she is in, I believe, in Washington, D.C. I think that event is tonight. And so she or maybe it's tomorrow night and she's traveling today. But either way, she's not going to be on today. She's not going
to be
Speaker 11: on tomorrow. I, in all likelihood, will do a members show tomorrow. So if you're not a member
of the
Speaker 11: group, great time to sign up. If someone drops a membership on your lap today, take advantage of that. Join us tomorrow. We'll have a little fun. But
I want to
Speaker 11: get into the open. Don't lose sight of the fact.
of
Speaker 11: the central recurring theme of the open.
Because I
Speaker 11: think you'll do really well to understand the open and then as we talk about the program. All right, so let's keep that in mind. Hey, hit the like button on your way in. YouTube has thrown the brakes on me over the last couple of weeks because of some shows that they had to throw yellow labels on. So hit the like button on the way in. That'll help push it up the distribution chain. And if you're not a subscriber, feel free to do that. But right now, ladies and gentlemen,
Speaker 12: right? Oh, hold on. Let me get it set up first.
I
Speaker 12: don't want to do the old open dance if the open's not yet set up.
Speaker 13: Ah, now, now, now.
Speaker 12: Ladies and gentlemen, here is your opening statement.
Everyone knows what it
Speaker 6: means to drink the Kool-Aid.
It's part of
Speaker 6: our common language. It means to unquestionably accept absurdity, even in the face
of what
Speaker 6: could be grave danger. It comes, of course, from the People's Temple in Guyana.
more
Speaker 6: commonly known as Jonestown for its leader, Jim Jones. The commonly accepted narrative is that Jones led a commune of around 800 or 900 people in Guyana and South America. After
a tragedy
Speaker 6: involving the death of a U.S. congressman and others, Jones ordered his people to drink the Kool-Aid, which they did without a second thought.
The
Speaker 6: mine conjures brainwashed followers voluntarily submitting to death at the whim of their dear leader. This is what happens, so goes the story, when religion runs amok. But
that's not
Speaker 6: exactly what happened. In
fact, that's
Speaker 6: not remotely
Speaker 1: what happened.
Jim Jones
Speaker 1: was not some itinerant preacher from Indiana who
moved a
Speaker 1: religious
Speaker 6: congregation from Indianapolis to San Francisco and later Guyana.
instead
Speaker 6: looking only at the facts
Speaker 14: and not common lore today. We're
not going to
Speaker 14: look at the common lore that's been embedded into the story. We're only
Speaker 6: looking at the facts today. The evidence points to Jim Jones as a long-term intelligence asset
running a
Speaker 6: large-scale intelligence experiment in the Guyana jungle. It points to testing mind-control drugs, obedience protocols, and other methods on a predominantly black and poor congregation.
We hear
Speaker 6: of the 1978 White Knight as a mass suicide, and perhaps some of the adherents voluntarily submitted to drinking the cyanide-laced Flavor-Aid. It wasn't Kool-Aid, it was a different
brand, but
Speaker 6: many didn't. They were killed when they refused. The reality of Jonestown is that it was the controlled termination of a compromised field trial
at a
Speaker 6: critical moment when the entire world might soon learn what had been going on in Guyana.
So
Speaker 6: Jones's
Speaker 8: intelligence ties trace all the way back to his roots in Indiana. He was born in 1931 in a little town called
Speaker 6: Crete, Indiana, but he grew up in Richmond, Indiana, just down the road.
It was there in
Speaker 6: Richmond, where as a teenager, he befriended a guy named Dan Mitrioni. Dan Mitrioni would play a recurring and important role
in Jim
Speaker 6: Jones's life. Dan Mitrioni was a local police officer, 11 years older than Jim Jones.
He was
Speaker 6: also known for his tough tactics and no-nonsense policing. Mitrioni later joined the U.S. government's Office of Public Safety. This was a program widely acknowledged as a CIA front. It went around training foreign police in counterinsurgency and interrogation techniques.
Mitrioni was
Speaker 6: stationed in Brazil starting in 1960. It's
there
Speaker 8: where he advised police in a town called Belo Horizonte.
This is
Speaker 6: precisely where Jim Jones relocated his family the following year, in 1961. Jim
Jones and his
Speaker 15: family lived in Bella Horizonte until 1963. Mitrioni's presence there made sense. He
was training
Speaker 6: local officers in methods that included psychological coercion. This further makes sense considering Bella Horizonte housed the CIA headquarters for the region.
Jim
Speaker 6: Jones's Brazilian sojourn remains one of the most mysterious chapters of his life.
Despite being
Speaker 6: a nearly destitute small-town preacher in Indiana, Jones
moves to
Speaker 6: Brazil and is suddenly flush with cash. He moved his wife and son there with him. Neighbors in Belo Horizonte later reported Jones receiving transportation, groceries, and even housing support from the local U.S. embassies.
Jones
Speaker 6: told neighbors he moved to Brazil to work with the U.S. Navy intelligence. Brazilian police reportedly monitored him as a suspected spy. One local, a guy named Marco Aurelio, who knew of Jones because he was dating a Temple member's daughter,
said a
Speaker 6: local detective tasked him to watch Jones because he was convinced Jones was with the CIA.
Speaker 15: Unfortunately, and perhaps coincidentally...
That
Speaker 15: detective died mysteriously before finishing his probe. Jones himself later admitted seeking out Mitrione's family in Brazil.
While in
Speaker 6: Brazil, Jim Jones studied local spiritist and voodoo practices, techniques involving drugs, rituals, and the power of suggestion to control people.
He returned to
Speaker 6: the U.S. in 1963 with the equivalent of today's money of over $100,000. When he got back, he immediately began expanding his church, the People's Temple.
And he
Speaker 15: built it into a multiracial socialist movement.
By the
Speaker 15: 1970s, key connections between Jim Jones and the U.S. intelligence community deepened.
The Layton
Speaker 15: family had become central to the People's Temple. The Layton family also had direct ties to
Speaker 6: U.S. chemical and biological warfare programs. Dr. Lawrence Layton, father of key Temple member Larry Layton, served as chief of chemical warfare for the U.S. Army.
He
Speaker 6: worked on projects involving behavior-modifying substances. His expertise aligned with the intelligence community's sub-projects on ethnic weaponry and mind control.
Larry Layton joined the
Speaker 6: temple and worked closely with Jim Jones. His sister, Deborah Layton, became one of Jones's most
Speaker 15: inner circle trustees.
Another Layton
Speaker 15: relative even handled the temple's finances.
The temple's
Speaker 15: practices eerily paralleled documented methods.
From the
Speaker 15: CIA's MKUltra program, heavy drugging, including sedatives, amphetamines, and psychotropics. These were administered covertly in food and drink. They practiced sleep deprivation, isolation, forced confession, mock executions, and even loyalty tests.
These
Speaker 6: techniques come straight from the CIA's programs. Declassified files show the CIA opened a file
Speaker 15: on Jim Jones around this time in Brazil. Well,
Speaker 15: and monitored the People's Temple extensively. FOIA releases confirm informants inside of Jonestown, surveillance of the group's leftist politics, and even a keen interest
Speaker 6: in its potential to discredit radical black socialist movements during the COINTELPRO's heyday.
The People's
Speaker 6: Temple's rapid growth in California gave it political cover, while serving as a controllable pressure valve for dissent.
In
Speaker 6: 1977,
Speaker 15: Jones moved over 900 of his followers from San Francisco, California, to Jonestown, Guyana. The Jonestown site is notable
Speaker 6: and remarkable not only for its remoteness, but also its proximity to the CIA. Guyana's
Speaker 15: Prime Minister, Forbes Burnham, received USAID support, widely believed
Speaker 6: to have come
from the
Speaker 6: CIA. The Jonestown settlement itself enjoyed broad embassy
Speaker 15: support.
there's a
Speaker 15: guy named congressman leo ryan he was a vocal critic of the cia a very vocal critic of the cia in fact he authored
Speaker 6: something called the hughes ryan amendment that required the intelligence community to notify congress of any
Speaker 15: covert operations you can imagine how well that went over inside intelligence circles
Ryan
Speaker 15: opened an investigation into Jonestown after relatives complained to him of abuses they alleged involved their family members. Congressman Ryan and a small delegation flew to Guyana to investigate the allegations in person. They arrived November 14, 1978. On November 18, 1978, Congressman Leo Ryan's delegation was leaving.
Speaker 15: That's when Temple gunmen ambushed the delegation as it was set to leave Guyana at the Port Kaituma airstrip. The group killed Congressman Ryan and four others. Larry Layton allegedly posed as a defector and opened fire from within the aircraft, wounding two people. When
news of the ambush
Speaker 15: made it back to the People's Temple compound, leader Jim Jones called
Speaker 6: everyone to the main meeting area.
Speaker 6: That's where he began ordering people to drink cyanide-laced flavor aid to cause their own deaths. It's all recorded. Those who refused appeared to have been put
Speaker 15: down with injections of the mixture.
Over the
Speaker 15: course of a few hours, more than 900 people died in the compound. Jones himself died from a head wound that many conclude is quite inconsistent with a person taking his own
life.
Speaker 6: After the event,
The
Speaker 6: U.S. military handled body removal, which is a little unusual for a foreign mass death.
It's not hard to
Speaker 6: look at the documented facts and
conclude that
Speaker 6: Jim Jones was not the one in charge.
If that's
Speaker 6: true, then the decision to liquidate everyone
Speaker 15: in the compound naturally starts to look more like the intelligence community shutting down an experiment and making sure there are no witnesses left to give their version of events.
Speaker 15: Congressman Ryan was a vehement opponent of the intelligence community. His visit threatened to expose an undisclosed intelligence operation. The easy way out is to remove both Congressman Ryan and shut down the operation and remove all witnesses at the same
Speaker 6: time. But
why would the
Speaker 6: intelligence community run a long-term op like this? And
the answer is
Speaker 6: we don't know exactly, but we can guess.
It
Speaker 6: could be to test mind-control drugs or maybe mind-control methods. Maybe
it's to
Speaker 6: discredit left-wing multiracial movements. Maybe it's to test crowd-control procedures. Or maybe it's just a way to find out how to cull
Speaker 15: undesirables from the population. But
what's clear to
Speaker 15: me as you look only at the facts and not at the mythical lore that has developed around Jim Jones, Jonestown, and Kool-Aid is that Jim Jones was an intelligence asset.
Speaker 15: Jonestown was a deadly end to a years-long field trial. And the more than 900 people who met their end in the jungle in Guyana,
they were
Speaker 15: expendable data points. That is your opening statement. I hope you enjoyed it as much as I did. I love that story. There's a great... Not everyone agrees with me on the intel part, by the way. I know there's dispute, which is why I tried to stick solely to the facts. I tried not to inject too much...
too much
Speaker 15: of the mythos into the story. I tried to really just stick to documented facts. In fact, I left a bunch out that I wanted to include because the
facts are
Speaker 15: disputed, even though they're documented.
There's a really good
Speaker 16: podcast called Transmissions from Jonestown. It's like 20 episodes long, but you really only need to listen to the first 10 or 12. They're
about an
Speaker 16: hour apiece, I think, give or take. And
Speaker 5: it's really, really good.
But I've
Speaker 5: always wondered about this. And as I look at TPUSA, as I look at Erika Fransfey, as I look at Charlie Kirk, as I look at people like Tyler Boyer and
Speaker 1: Andrew Colvitt and all the people at the top of TPUSA, I keep coming back to this Jonestown type experiment. Because
I ask myself, why would the
Speaker 8: CIA have been running all of the, you know, Colts were huge in the 50s, 60s, 70s, and 80s, and then they sort of fizzled out. After David Koresh died in the 1990s, Colts really didn't have much
I
Speaker 8: mean, there aren't
Speaker 16: really many left anymore. There was the Way International. There was the Children of God.
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): There was Heaven's Gate. There was obviously the
Speaker 18: People's Temple. You had the Manson family. I mean, you just had all
Speaker 8: these cults that popped up all over the country. They really were all over the country. And
then they
Speaker 8: sort of fizzled out. It's as if there was a program
that.
to
Speaker 8: run a bunch of simultaneous experiments at the same time, see what worked, and then shut down that program and start applying it to the real world. That's what I think about a lot of these groups like TPUSA. I think a lot of their programs, a lot of the things they do, a lot of their talking points, a lot of their manipulation tactics, I think are drawn out of this intelligence community. I really do.
And tonight I
Speaker 8: want to give you the missing year.
Speaker 19: I want to show you a little bit about the missing year.
Speaker 19: Because I think it's pretty damning.
It's pretty
Speaker 9: damning. I'm going to show you a brief clip from Candice yesterday because she sort of sets up by asking the question, where was Erica Kirk in 2017? And what the heck was she doing?
And so I want to play this for you real quick. And then I want to answer the
Speaker 8: question. Because she asked about Elm Group. I've got the answer. She asked about where Erica was. I've got the answer. I didn't know she needed this. All she had to do was
Speaker 20 (higher-pitched voice): ask. Candice. Candice.
Your
Speaker 20 (higher-pitched voice): humble host is at the standby ready to answer your questions.
You don't have to
Speaker 20 (higher-pitched voice): ask your multi-million listeners. You could just ask your humble host.
You can
Speaker 20 (higher-pitched voice): text me. I'll tell you the answer. Nevertheless, nevertheless,
Speaker 21: here she goes. I want you to hear it from her. Here's what she was looking for. And I'll show you today how we're able to answer questions from yesterday.
Speaker 22: 2017, Erica is going to get busy. But once again, we're not going to really understand everything.
Speaker 22: what she's actually
Speaker 23: doing, okay? She's doing everything and nothing at the same time, always reminding you. This is a 29-year-old woman. She's about to be 30. You can't just like not do something in life unless you're unspeakably wealthy. I guess that could be the lifestyle, but that's not the circumstance. I want to pause
it
Speaker 24: right there to say something.
If you
Speaker 25: look at Erica's official biography, if you look at her official CV, I guess you would say, or her LinkedIn
Speaker 5: page, there is no job that Erica Francois has until she goes to work at, opens this mythical company called Proclaim Streetwear in 2018, 2019. She doesn't really have a job. She claims to be working at Corcoran Group in 2018, but for 2015, 16, and 17, there's really nothing.
Speaker 5: Now, we know in 2013 and 14, we know exactly
Speaker 9: where she was. She was globetrotting with her basketball-playing boyfriend shacking up around the world. We know that. So we got her from 2012 to 2014. We know where she was.
Then for
Speaker 19: 2014 and 15, she starts dating this J.T. Massey, and she's spending a lot of time in Scottsdale and a lot of time in Oklahoma where he was playing ball. So we know where she was then. But then I guess they break up at some
Speaker 9: point, and we lose her because she claims to have moved to New York City.
But
Speaker 9: there's no job associated with her moving to New York City.
And so this is this black
Speaker 9: hole from 2015 to
Speaker 8: 2018, where we don't know where she was. Now, it's possible she's just sponging off the old lady. I guess that's a possibility. But
tonight we'll answer the
Speaker 5: question because I don't think that's
exactly
Speaker 26: right. I
don't think
Speaker 26: that's exactly right. We're going to get some details tonight that we have not had before.
for
Speaker 27: Erica Kirk. On January 12th,
Speaker 23: she establishes the Elm Group LLC. Okay. No idea what this company does. We're
going
Speaker 28: to answer that question tonight. I'll tell you exactly what it does.
So
Speaker 23: nothing makes sense in terms of what this company does. I could not figure out what this company does. If you know, please let me know. Maybe you've worked with the Elm Group. I'm going
to go
Speaker 23: with Erica's kind of doing what her mom does and just creating a lot of LLCs. There's no description that is offered on those documents. On February 1st, as you guys may have seen, she then appears in this documentary that's called Black Start by Patria Patrick. The documentary also features the CIA director, James Woolsey. Now, I want to say...
Speaker 23: This documentary is about EMP attacks, right? How the government needs to prepare for them. So it's a bit more of her mother's propaganda, so to speak. And she is going to present her mother's business model. I'll let you take a listen to a quick clip of this. I'm
Speaker 5: playing this clip on purpose
Speaker 24: because it's going to play into my hypothesis of what Erica is doing in 2017 when I show you the receipts. Yeah.
We have
Speaker 29: five major threats that make our grid extremely vulnerable that we've presented to congressional
Speaker 30 (higher-pitched voice): officials. One being cyber, two being hackers, three being physical threats, fourth one is solar EMP, and the fifth one is man-made
Speaker 31: EMP.
Speaker 32: So the concern that we have is that we put out this critical information and when we go over this risk
Speaker 33: analysis they hear what we're saying but they don't want to take
action.
and candace goes on to
Speaker 34: ask the obvious question the
hell is
Speaker 35: she doing in this production
i
Speaker 5: think it's a legitimate
question i asked
Speaker 5: myself the same question i had one time i said well i guess she was trying to be an actress her mom's trying to sell a product she fancies herself as beautiful and amazing and everything she does so why can't i star in your documentary or your basically delayed long advertisement listen,
And I
Speaker 5: just assumed this was like a 30 or 60 minute
Speaker 14: advertisement for her mom's EMP company. Made sense to me.
I'm not so
Speaker 14: sure anymore.
I'm not so sure anymore. Whatever it was
Speaker 14: to get the director of the CIA into your program, whether it's a movie, whether it's a documentary, whether it's an advertisement for a company, that's kind of an interesting thing. If you wanted to
Speaker 5: do that, you could not pick up the phone and get the CIA director. I promise you.
If you
Speaker 5: said, hey, I'm filming an ad for my company. Can I borrow the director of the CIA? All I need him to do is sit there and look good. I'll have a pretty girl up front talking through some talking points. Is that okay with you? You're going to hear no. You're going to hear absolutely not. Go away. We hate you.
That's just
Speaker 7: reality. That's what's going to happen. I
don't mean to be
Speaker 7: the one to point it out, but that is what's going to happen.
They're going
Speaker 7: to tell you to buzz off.
As
Speaker 7: they, as
Speaker 36: they should, as they should, we don't need people doing it. All right. So this
is going to be fun. We have got
Speaker 37: to answer the question where in the world was
Speaker 38: Erica Kirk during 2017? And I've got to play this.
Which one do
Speaker 38: I want to put this on? I
think I
Speaker 39: want to put it on this one.
No, I want to put it on this. All right.
i've got a slide deck
Speaker 40: for you because she had a slide deck in her video so what not wrong wrong one wrong one still the wrong one
there we go i have
Speaker 40: got a slide
deck
Speaker 41: for you where in the world is erica franzveit allegedly allegedly so let's start to
begin with if you
Speaker 35: kept
Speaker 9: watching the candace clip and i didn't want to she mentioned she did not know what the elm group was
because
Speaker 9: she opens this LLC called
Speaker 12: the Elm Group in 2016, September of 2016. Well, there's
nobody like
Speaker 42: Daisy to
Speaker 43: dig up dirt. Oop,
hit the
Speaker 43: wrong button.
Back, back,
Speaker 43: back, back, back. All right.
Erica Lane
Speaker 43: Management is what it's called. Erica Lane
Speaker 6: Fransfey is her name. Apparently, she thought Erica Lane
Speaker 9: Management sounded good.
So
Speaker 9: Erica Lane Management is the Elm Group. She opened two websites on the same day, ericalanemanagement.com and elm.group.
And if you'll
Speaker 9: notice, elmgroup is the name of it, and it is filed on January 12th. So she
Speaker 19: opens the websites up shortly before she files it. So I think
Speaker 15: any reasonable, logical person can conclude these are
the
Speaker 15: websites associated with that.
So if
Speaker 15: you want to know what ELM stands for,
Speaker 9: it's Erica Lane Management. Now, if you go to her archived
Speaker 5: page, and I will do that now, if you go back to ericafransfay.com,
this is
Speaker 5: her website as it appeared, August 5th, 2021, ericafransfay.com, and you slide down to the contact portion down here.
see how it
Speaker 5: says contact if you hover over this and you click it i'm not going to click it because it'll open up my
Speaker 9: email but that email goes to agent at elm.group that's where it goes so if you're wanting to contact erica franceve
Speaker 44: back in the days
she was basically
Speaker 8: representing herself she opened a company called elm group llc and elm group served as the agent to erica lane franceve
Erica
Speaker 8: Lane Management represented Erica Lane Fransfrey. So when she claims all this time to have been an agency represented model, I'm not so sure about that because she was the
Speaker 9: agency. She was the agency. So if
you want
Speaker 9: to put that together now.
After we
Speaker 9: find this.
Speaker 12: And
we realize she's
Speaker 12: doing something, we're not sure what.
We start
Speaker 12: finding that.
erica's
Speaker 12: trip
Speaker 1: advisor profile it was a gold mine because we were able to find out everywhere she went during
Speaker 8: 2016 or 2017 you go back and you can look
for
Speaker 45: example in march of 2017 she was at the baglioni hotel regina and
Speaker 9: they had stunning and spacious rooms she loved the breakfast the food was fresh
and the
Speaker 9: cappuccinos were amazing
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): I'll see
Speaker 9: you next
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): time.
The
Speaker 9: piano player at night was
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): awesome as well. Great restaurants and walking distance, only 15 minutes away from everything. Walking distance to the Spanish steps as well.
Trip type,
Speaker 9: traveled with friends.
So in March of
Speaker 9: 2017, she's traveling with friends.
It's nice that
Speaker 9: she tells us what she's doing here because, yes, she's traveling with friends,
but
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): wait until you see what else she's doing.
Then she goes to a
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): different location in Rome.
the
Speaker 9: gorgeous view very touristy these are the spanish steps great spot to walk around shop and people watch she's nosy skyline
view of
Speaker 9: rome is tremendous super crowded on the weekends tourists and
Speaker 12: locals keep your belongings close to you
truly beautiful
Speaker 12: weaving in and out
Speaker 19: of the streets finding fun little cafes and unique shops amongst the big name
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): couture brands have your camera ready great spots for photos so she's
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): She's into the trip advisor thing for some reason at this time.
This is the
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): Piazza del Campo in Rome.
Same month,
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): March of 20... Oh, this is Siena, Italy. Excuse me, Siena, Italy.
This has to be
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): one of the most beautiful plazas in the world.
The
Speaker 46: history here is so rich. Everyone's so nice. Food amazing as well. I'm assuming this was the same friend's trip and
that they
Speaker 46: just
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): toured around
Italy a
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): little bit. Then she goes to an incredible restaurant for dinner. I have no idea what she's doing for money during this time, by the way. Again, maybe sponging off her old lady. Maybe, well,
we'll figure
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): that out in a second. There might be some other business she's doing while she's over there. You got bottles of unique wine. I didn't
Speaker 16: think she drank at this period of time. She said she didn't drink leading
up to
Speaker 16: Charlie Kirk, but apparently she did. Fish
was
Speaker 5: incredibly fresh. That'll be a
relief to
Speaker 5: everyone who saw the Filet of Fish Instagram post.
They
Speaker 5: have fresh fish here, not Filet-O-Fish.
Staff accommodating, very
Speaker 47: romantic inside.
Raises the
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): question. I didn't think she dated for five years leading up to
Speaker 46: Charlie Kirk, but they have gluten-free options for pasta.
Then she
Speaker 46: goes to Città del Vaticano, Vatican City.
Took a quick
Speaker 46: trip here before leaving
Speaker 45: Rome.
Speaker 45: didn't make it inside the Vatican. Had a chance to browse the shops around St. Peter's Square, take in the spectacular view of the cathedral from afar. Well worth the experience,
Speaker 49: even if you're there only 20
Speaker 8: minutes. So now she is leaving Rome.
Now she's leaving
Speaker 8: Rome.
Speaker 50 (higher-pitched voice): We assume the whole Rome trip was friends.
Now she goes to
Speaker 50 (higher-pitched voice): Florence, and now look, she's no longer traveling with friends. Now she's changed it to traveled with family.
She's now traveling
Speaker 50 (higher-pitched voice): with family.
Same
Speaker 9: month.
March
Speaker 9: of 2017, can't rave enough about this hotel, the Portrait Firenze. By far, one of the most incredible experiences. Decor is fantastic,
Speaker 46: clean and modern. Just hyping the
place up,
Speaker 46: really. I'm not going to read the whole thing. But
this is
Speaker 46: now, she's in Florence and she's traveling with
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): family. There's a little picture of her there in the mirror. I don't know if you can see that. She's down here in the foreground of the mirror here.
We
Speaker 46: had to blur this part out here. YouTube's been weird about our channel lately. So we had to cover David's wang. But
you guys know
Speaker 46: what a wang looks like. So you're not missing anything. Here she's
at the
Speaker 46: statue of David at the Galleria del
Speaker 52: Academia. Major item on our must-see list. It did not disappoint.
the
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): museum and the statue of david are so inspiring and beautifully moving wish we would have had time to take a tour guide
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): with with us please do yourself a favor
and go uh
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): still in florence this time at piazza
della
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): signora signoria i don't speak italian by the way i don't know if that's been obvious
so far area was
Speaker 8: gorgeous loved walking through it all night with my family so her family is
there her
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): family's there
The way
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): statues were lit up was so beautiful, very empowering, especially if you know the history behind everything, can really be crowded during the day. Stays in Florence and now
Speaker 54: is at a museum, the Museo Salvatore Ferragamo. If I
have any Italian
Speaker 55: speakers, this is the best I can do. It's truly spectacular to see all the original works of Salvatore Ferragamo.
Speaker 19: Gave
her a renewed
Speaker 19: perspective, especially
Speaker 46: on the brand. I had never heard of it, but.
a little
Speaker 46: fun little mid-morning
Speaker 56: activity, got passes from the hotel. Then
they go
Speaker 56: to the Piazza del Duomo. You'll
not be able to
Speaker 56: take enough photos of the Duomo. This is in Italy, one
of her
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): favorite top experiences in Florence. Be blown away. Regardless if you're Christian or not, it's a must-see. And
then they have dinner,
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): incredible food
Speaker 12: and romantic ambiance. Now, she's with her family. This is a little weird, by the way.
But I guess
Speaker 12: maybe you can recognize romantic ambiance even if you're with your family. But
they had a great
Speaker 12: dinner at La Giostra, La
Speaker 46: Giostra. Recommendation from the hotel, portion sizes were large to accommodate her large knuckles. You could definitely split meals. Ambiance with the lighting was beautiful and very romantic. Pasta was unreal delicious. And
now she's in
Speaker 46: Chianti, Italy. Chianti.
Gorgeous
Speaker 46: place, right through the gates, you'll be greeted at
Speaker 49: the entrance of the winery. So I'm reading these so you can tell that she's clearly just traveling the first time in Rome with friends, the second time in Florence and
Speaker 44: Chianti with family,
because that's not
Speaker 19: going to remain the theme through the rest of these. But
I want you
Speaker 19: to know that this is what she's doing here, allegedly.
the Via
Speaker 19: Della Volte. They stopped there
along
Speaker 45: the way to the winery.
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): It was an amazing experience to walk around and see the incredible stonework, little shops, dining places. So charming and romantic. Loves the word romantic, by the
way. Loves the
Speaker 46: word romantic. Would
have loved to spend
Speaker 46: a little more time browsing around. Also loved you to get a true feel, a feel of true authentic Italian culture. So glad we stopped you.
Good for
Speaker 46: her. Now,
there's a
Speaker 57 (lower-pitched voice): picture of a male in here. I don't know if he works here or if he was with them or if that's a boyfriend. I don't know who that is on the right.
Could
Speaker 57 (lower-pitched voice): just be a, you know, rando there, but that's
one of
Speaker 57 (lower-pitched voice): the pictures.
Walking around town
Speaker 57 (lower-pitched voice): stumbled upon Rocco di
Speaker 58: Castellina. It
was incredible
Speaker 58: to see, area perfect for a day trip from Florence. So
many amazing areas to
Speaker 58: take photos of, especially the little church.
Now they're in
Speaker 58: Siena, Italy. They moved from Florence to Chianti to Siena.
you got to do
Speaker 58: yourself a favor and go visit Siena's Cathedral, sacred
place
Speaker 45: to not only breathtaking rich in history, but absolutely life-changing. Her life was changed in March
Speaker 59: of 2017. Did you guys know that? I
had no
Speaker 59: idea. But
it was life-changing. She was walking around with
Speaker 60: her jaw on the
Speaker 46: ground, just completely stunned, be ready to take a ton of photos.
Speaker 46: More Siena, Italy. They went to Centro Storico di Siena, the World Heritage Strip. Loved roaming around
Speaker 49: everywhere you turn was amazing. So now she's in Paris. Now
she's in
Speaker 49: Paris. Can you see what's
Speaker 50 (higher-pitched voice): happening right here, the trip type? Can
you see the
Speaker 50 (higher-pitched voice): change in the trip type? We're
now in
Speaker 44: April. She was in March in Rome, in Florence, in Chianti, and Siena.
That
Speaker 8: was with family and friends. Now she's in Paris in
April of
Speaker 8: 2017. And if you look at the trip type, it's changed.
Speaker 19: It's no longer traveling with friends or traveling with family. Now she's traveling on business. I
don't know if you
Speaker 19: can see that. It's right there above the far left picture, right below the highlighted date of story.
Trip type
Speaker 19: traveled on business. The hell business is she doing in Paris?
What is she doing in Paris
Speaker 50 (higher-pitched voice): on business?
And I can assure
Speaker 50 (higher-pitched voice): you, this is not the last time I'm going to ask this question. Keep
in mind,
Speaker 50 (higher-pitched voice): there's no entry in her resume or LinkedIn or
Speaker 61: any part of the Erica Fransvet narrative leading up to meeting Charlie Kirk that would explain what she was doing that would require international travel or really doing it all.
Speaker 3: yeah i saw i saw somebody in the comments say the last trip in italy said may 6th so there's two dates on each slide one is the date she reviewed
Speaker 5: the uh destination and
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): then one is the date the month of
that she
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): that she was there
so she
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): was there in march she reviewed it in may
Speaker 49: so that's the confusion
there but now
Speaker 49: she's in business
Speaker 54: now she's in a hotel for business in Paris.
Speaker 54: Never have enough amazing things to say about this hotel. Rooms were pristine and extremely clean. Staff was
Speaker 19: amazing and very attentive. Our room had an incredible balcony. The concierge was extremely helpful when it came to making reservations. The Athene is the place to stay in Paris. I'm
Speaker 46: going to look something
up because I
Speaker 46: did not look it up for this one, but I looked it up for a few of the other ones.
So a
Speaker 56: night at the Athene, if you want to stay there, is, let's see here. One
of these hotels she was in was
Speaker 56: like $4,000
a
Speaker 63 (lower-pitched voice): night. This is about $2,000 a night if you want to stay at the Athene. So it's not like she's staying at the Best
Speaker 36: Western. She's
staying at very
Speaker 36: luxurious places. On business, no less. On business.
Speaker 36: According to Ms. Fransfey.
Now she goes
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): to the Eiffel Tower.
Spectacular view
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): of the Eiffel Tower from her hotel. But to see it up close was everything and more.
Highly recommend
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): you make this touristy attraction, but you'll be fine visiting just the outside.
Unless you really
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): have it
on your
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): bucket list to go to the top.
Then she goes to the
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): Ritz
Speaker 3: Paris.
I
Speaker 3: looked up a call, a one night at the Ritz Paris starts at around $3,500 a night, goes up to about 5,000 a night
per night,
Speaker 3: not months
Speaker 4: income, not months take-home pay, one night to slumber. You
know, you check
Speaker 3: in at three and you're out by 11 the next morning, $3,500
is where
Speaker 3: it starts. The
Ritz in general
Speaker 8: never disappoints, meaning she stays at the Ritz often.
I had
Speaker 8: no idea she came from this kind of money.
There's nothing like
Speaker 64: the
Speaker 45: Paris location. This
is a top hotel
Speaker 45: you must visit if you're not staying there. Quiet area that it is in with all the high-end shopping is great. Our main purpose was going to have tea and a light lunch at the outdoor patio area, and it was such a relaxing experience. Service is slow, so pan accordingly. But
that is the
Speaker 45: Ritz
Speaker 46: Paris. Stunning.
She
Speaker 46: says of Point Alexandre III, Point Alexandre III, I think it's French as trois. Gorgeous
area, especially on a
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): rainy day with overcast clouds, bringing out the strong contrast from the bridge and water. Great area to walk around.
Still in April
Speaker 46: 2017 in Paris, she goes to the Cathedral Notre Dame de Paris. Now
you thought my
Speaker 46: Italian was
Speaker 3: bad, my French is worse.
But
Speaker 3: she toured some after tour. Listen, this is such a snotty
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): thing to say. She's clowning on the Notre Dame Cathedral.
After
Speaker 65: touring some of the Duomos throughout Tuscany, it was really hard to compare the Notre Dame Cathedral since it's
Speaker 66: a completely different form of architecture. There's this theme is already bubbling up about
Speaker 67: architecture in Catholic churches. Remember, that was Charlie's reason for going architecture. He didn't
Speaker 68: like the spirituality. He liked the architecture.
He just
Speaker 60: wanted to sit in a pretty building.
It's a stunning
Speaker 60: area. Our Uber
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): driver recommended we walk from the
back to
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): the front
because he
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): thought the back was more powerful, and he was absolutely right.
It's a
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): must-visit, very iconic and impressive, a line outside. Don't worry, it moves fast. So
again, remember, she's
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): here on business.
Speaker 46: I'm
going to
Speaker 46: guess the Champalesee.
Loved walking around
Speaker 21: this area. Must visit if you're in Paris. Doesn't matter if you're first or 100th time visiting. Great shopping, dining, and people watching. Back to people watching. That's
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): a little creepy. Fantastic areas to take photos. Old buildings are gorgeous. Even the bridges are stunning. Keep your eyes open for little locks all over the base of the statue on the bridges.
Speaker 69: I
guess I could try to
Speaker 70 (lower-pitched voice): pronounce this. Hold, please. This
is the
Speaker 25: Musée des...
Speaker 25: the best
Speaker 71: i can do guys no
idea
Speaker 19: what to expect but the moment i walked into this museum i was overwhelmed with how gorgeous these massive
Speaker 57 (lower-pitched voice): panoramic monet paintings were highly recommend you visiting this museum worth it and incredibly
moving now she's to the
Speaker 46: louvre the world famous louvre so
happy i
Speaker 46: visited this place such a bucket list museum and experience the line went buy really fast. Museum stores are awesome for gifts.
also
Speaker 46: attached to a food court and mini mall. One
of the
Speaker 46: favorite parts of the trip.
Now she's in
Speaker 50 (higher-pitched voice): Chile. Chile, Santiago, Chile. So she was in Paris on business.
She was in Rome
Speaker 49: with friends.
She was in
Speaker 49: Florence, Chianti, and Siena
with family. Then
Speaker 55: she's in Paris on business.
and
Speaker 63 (lower-pitched voice): now she's in Santiago on business. Hang on, I'm getting a note here.
Oh, traveled as a
Speaker 72: couple. So she's got a squeeze
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): that she's traveling with in Paris. I wonder
if the
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): squeeze was also there on business.
Santiago,
Speaker 36: Chile.
Speaker 36: Santiago, Chile. We don't
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): know yet, but I'll tell you, she's there on business. Was looking for a good latte or
Speaker 46: cappuccino, not from Starbucks. It was okay. Oh, the poor
Speaker 45: Tavali.
Their batido
Speaker 45: doce latte was good. Their milk alternative options are soy milk.
Well, so sorry that happened
Speaker 74: to you, my dear lady.
Hard to
Speaker 74: get a good cup of coffee in Santiago, Chile.
This place has
Speaker 3: awesome burgers, Danes. Now, I don't know if it compares to an In-N-Out burger. You know, she loves eating her In-N-Out burger. Why would she go on an Egyptian plane when she could just sit around eating In-N-Out burgers and eating chocolate shakes?
So I don't, I
Speaker 75: don't. Oh,
the pics aren't
Speaker 76: hers. Okay, that's fair enough.
But that did
Speaker 76: look like her.
That did
Speaker 47: look like her.
Speaker 46: Um, but the, uh, um, Dane's bar and restaurante in Santiago
Speaker 19: only earns four circles from Miss France Faye, but it is awesome. Stumbled upon this place between meetings at
Speaker 77 (higher-pitched voice): the Hyatt. What meetings are between meetings? You have multiple meetings at the Hyatt. What are you doing in Santiago, Chile, having meetings at hotels?
Speaker 8: That's a little weird.
Remember her meeting
Speaker 8: in
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): Paris was at a hotel.
nice
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): little spot nice modern diner type vibes their burgers were fresh as well as the lettuce and french fries thought it was cute they gave you a little bucket of popcorn prior to your meal i'm gluten free so they wrapped
my
Speaker 49: burger in lechuga
Speaker 36: let's come on let's speak the language erica it's lechuga
lettuce for
Speaker 36: you non-espanol speakers
she
Speaker 36: has two meetings, at least two meetings at the highest guys. I don't
want to be the one to
Speaker 79: point it out.
But if you're in back-to-back
Speaker 3: meetings at a hotel, there's, you know, possibilities start to open themselves.
it was
Speaker 46: our first meal in santiago and it did not disappoint this is a little place called coco the sea bass
wrapped in
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): shrimp was awesome and so were the appetizers great peruvian restaurant uh
that's cool but
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): you're in chile but
Speaker 41: whatever peru's close right who's counting what's a few hundred miles between friends
Speaker 14: earned four circles. She's a tough grader,
by the
Speaker 14: way. To get five circles, you
got to
Speaker 14: really be, you know, step it up a notch for her. I
wouldn't want her
Speaker 14: walking into my
Speaker 54: restaurant. This is Plaza de Armas. You're looking to get the full downtown Santiago experience. This is the area
to
Speaker 46: walk around. Changing of the
guard is
Speaker 46: around 12 p.m. Make sure you hold on to your belongings and be fully aware.
But
Speaker 46: nonetheless, a great area to have a coffee and stroll around and see the true culture. Where can you go that you just set your belongings down? This is the second time
Speaker 80: she's mentioned watch your belongings.
Now she's at a beautiful cathedral in Santiago. Having been
Speaker 54: all over Europe and getting blown away by the Duomos in Italy, it's hard to have an unbiased
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): eye.
but
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): this cathedral was beautiful. We went around 12 p.m., and all their cadets were having mass. Pretty cool experience. The area around it is almost like a little park. Small, but great to stop and sit on a bench and enjoy the weather, coffee, and people watching. Back to people watching. I'm
a little
Speaker 74: nervous when, like, 20% of your reviews are about staring at people. We
found a great
Speaker 74: artist there that we
bought a
Speaker 74: painting from.
Speaker 3: now she's at a different hotel. Remember, she was at the Hyatt on business in Santiago, Chile. Now she's at the Hilton Garden Inn by the
Speaker 81: airport on business. Had
business meetings
Speaker 81: here all day. Why
didn't you stay at
Speaker 82 (higher-pitched voice): the Hyatt? You were at the Hyatt already having business meetings. Why
did you
Speaker 82 (higher-pitched voice): change hotels I
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): don't
Speaker 8: know.
To
Speaker 82 (higher-pitched voice): have all day worth of business meetings, plural, meetings, plural.
The breakfast buffet
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): was complimentary
and pretty
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): decent considering it
was a
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): buffet. The staff was very accommodating. It's a great spot for a rooftop
Speaker 8: sunset also.
What business
Speaker 8: is she doing in Paris and Santiago,
Speaker 77 (higher-pitched voice): Chile?
I have to
Speaker 77 (higher-pitched voice): know.
I
Speaker 77 (higher-pitched voice): have to know because
Speaker 83: can't think of too many innocent reasons that like
Speaker 14: you, you were not in any kind of international trade that I'm aware of.
You were not in
Speaker 7: any kind of,
I don't
Speaker 7: know. I don't, what are you doing?
I
Speaker 8: think it's a question that needs to be answered. This was just a year or so before she meets Charlie Kirk and turns his life upside down and ends up taking over his organization. I want
to know what she's
Speaker 84: doing. Is she working for an intelligence agency? Because that's kind of what it seems like. Are you working as a
woman of the
Speaker 85: night? I mean, I don't know. I don't think so. I don't, I'm not suggesting that, but I mean, there's,
Speaker 85: There are only
Speaker 7: so many things you can do where you have back-to-back meetings in hotels all day.
Like if you're going to meet someone for business, you
Speaker 4: go to their office.
You don't fly
Speaker 74: into Santiago, Chile and say, I don't want to drive over to your office. Just come to my hotel. That's weird.
i don't want to
Speaker 86: speculate too much without
Speaker 87: knowing more but i think these findings alone merit a response of some sort what were you doing because
Speaker 18: depending on the answer that question it might have a lot to do with why you were
eager
Speaker 14: to meet charlie and i'm sorry you were eager to meet Charlie?
it
Speaker 88 (lower-pitched voice): took three approaches to finally get the job done, but
you run into him in
Speaker 88 (lower-pitched voice): Jerusalem.
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): You
run into him at
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): the grand opening of the turning point USA headquarters. For some reason you're there when you're not in politics.
And then you run into
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): him when he wants you to come work for the faith component
Speaker 12: of TP USA. What was your job?
What
Speaker 12: were you doing?
Because you
Speaker 61: leave this life here and you go to New York and you go sit for the
real estate exam. I don't know what
Speaker 47: business you're traveling on.
Business in the
Speaker 91: hotel in Paris, business at the hotel in Chile,
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): business at the hotel, a
different hotel
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): in Chile. Business at the Hyatt in Chile and now business at
the...
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): Hilton Garden Inn in Chile.
Now she's
Speaker 7: arrived in New York City, the city she supposedly lives in. Notice the reviews. She
supposedly lives here at
Speaker 7: this time, by the way.
Yet she's reviewing the hotels. Why are you reviewing
Speaker 20 (higher-pitched voice): the hotels? This is one of my favorite hotels in New York City. I
Speaker 9: love staying here. You live there, supposedly.
Speaker 9: At this point in time, you're supposed to live in New York City. Why are you in hotels?
The rooms are modern and
Speaker 19: extremely comfortable. The accommodations are incredible. The location is hard to beat as well. Absolutely love the bar area. The restaurant's a great place for afternoon tea or to have business meetings.
What business meetings are
Speaker 92: you doing in hotels all day long, all over the globe?
The furnishings
Speaker 5: and, of course, the crystal make this hotel a spectacle all in itself. Again, I have to ask,
what business
Speaker 16: meetings are
you doing
Speaker 16: in a hotel in Paris? What business meetings are you doing at a hotel in Chile? What business are you doing at a different hotel in Chile? And what business meetings are you doing in New
Speaker 3: York City? And why are you in a hotel in New York City when you supposedly live on Madison Avenue? 121 Madison Avenue, apartment 5G.
She doesn't live
Speaker 3: there anymore. That's not doxing. They don't have that department.
Our
Speaker 9: companies go to what company? What company do you work for, Erica?
What company do
Speaker 9: you work
Speaker 54: for?
I
Speaker 54: absolutely love this spot for lunch and drinks. The ambiance is fantastic. The service is awesome. Their food is also great. Highly recommend this place for a breakaway from
Speaker 93: the Soho hustle and bustle. I
just thought of something. I want to look
Speaker 94: something up in the. I
want to look something up
Speaker 94: real quick.
I
Speaker 56: wanted to look Crosby up in the Einstein files. There's
too many
Speaker 95: responses. I'll
have to look that up
Speaker 95: later. But
what company are you
Speaker 96: working for? Because there's no company on your resume. There's no company on your LinkedIn.
you claim
Speaker 61: to have been working for yourself at this point in time by yourself. Like
if you
Speaker 61: hear her tell her life story
Speaker 1: in 2017, she was running her nonprofit. She was running. That's it. She had nothing else to do. She wasn't, didn't
work
Speaker 16: in a real estate company. She
didn't get her
Speaker 16: license till the following year.
She didn't have employees. So
Speaker 97: what, what company were you working for? Again, Thank
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): you.
If you had
Speaker 97: a company in 2017, I think
you should
Speaker 97: tell us who it was.
I think you should tell us who it was. This is the New York edition. This is a
Speaker 98: hotel. I
love coming here for
Speaker 98: meetings during the day.
The
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): sitting area in the first level is very simple and relaxing. Easy to tuck away in a corner and get some quiet time away from the hustle and bustle of the city. Service is great as well. I highly recommend
Speaker 99: this place for business meetings or quick meetups. Oh, interesting. Erica,
what business meetings are you
Speaker 1: having all over the globe? And
why do they all take place
Speaker 100: in hotels?
This
Speaker 57 (lower-pitched voice): is another New York City, May of 2017. Cute little find for a Wednesday afternoon meeting. I
wish there were more
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): seating options, especially
Speaker 88 (lower-pitched voice): with the weekly lunch rush. Their salad options were great. I wish there were more gluten-free vegan options. Love, love, love their dirty chai.
If you know where
Speaker 14: she worked, please email
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): me, realbaronpodcast at gmail.com. I would love to know where she was working in 2017, that she has all of these business meetings, that she has our company. Now
she's reviewing the train
Speaker 37: station, ladies and gentlemen. She's reviewing the train station. This is an interesting review,
Speaker 19: though, if you read through it.
This is her
Speaker 19: preferred method of traveling throughout the East
Speaker 102: Coast on N-Track, especially to D.C. What
are you
Speaker 102: doing in D.C.?
Just make sure of what track
Speaker 103: you're
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): getting on.
It can get
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): overwhelming at time. Food options are what you would expect. Jamba juice to Nathan's hot dogs. Highly suggest, especially if you're a woman, do not travel throughout Penn Station alone at night. A ton of homeless people find this place a safe haven, especially during the midnight hours, to just be fully aware of your surroundings. Why
are you going to
Speaker 61: D.C. regularly? Remember, I want to flash back for a moment.
Okay.
I want to
Speaker 61: flashback for just a moment. Do you remember when she was
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): communicating with that 15-year-old girl relatively inappropriately, allegedly? One
of the things she
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): said on her Twitter feed was that she was very involved in D.C. politics. She was justifying having tattoos. And
she was
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): saying, I have white tattoos on my hands, and it doesn't stop me. I am very involved in politics in Washington, D.C. That was 2015.
that
Speaker 105: was 2015. So
in
Speaker 61: 2015, she's very active in Washington, D.C. In 2017, she's traveling all over the
Speaker 6: globe having business meetings in hotels. And
in May of
Speaker 6: 2017, she's still going to D.C. via Amtrak. It's her preferred method. I
just find that
Speaker 106: shocking. I find that interesting to me.
I find that
Speaker 107: inexplicable when you look at her history. This
is
Speaker 46: Sistina, great spot for some high-end and expensive Italian. Every time I go here with my uncle, we have a great time. The food is fresh,
and we
Speaker 46: usually order the specials. Service
is slow
Speaker 46: at times, especially if the restaurant is
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): packed, but overall a very welcoming and enjoyable experience. I don't know who the uncle is. I can assume this is Uncle Alan Rothstein, who's
really not her uncle at
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): all. He's an uncle...
by way
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): of marriage to a marriage that doesn't exist anymore. He's just a guy. At one point, his mom was married into the family is kind of the extent of it.
I'm assuming that's the
Speaker 108: uncle, but I don't know.
And she's in D.C. in
Speaker 109: June in Arlington, Virginia.
Absolute
Speaker 110: must see.
Please be
Speaker 110: reverent and respectful when
walking
Speaker 111: through the cemetery.
Speaker 111: Honoring the brave men and women who sacrificed their lives for our freedom. So much history.
Now she's back in
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): New York.
When was
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): she in D.C.? June. So in July, she's back in New York.
Came here for
Speaker 99: a work dinner. Shocking. She didn't work anywhere, guys. I'm
grateful they put us in
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): the back area so it was quieter. Food was fantastic. Appetizer-wise, love the peppers.
Everything that
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): was ordered, the dinner party enjoyed. I can see why it's always so busy.
I have
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): no idea what she did.
Then to
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier. Spends a lot of time around military gear during this wayward era where she's not actually employed anywhere, but having business meetings all over the globe. Cannot
Speaker 58: express to my friends and family who visit D.C. to make a special trip to the cemetery to witness
the
Speaker 57 (lower-pitched voice): Changing of the guard of the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier. Please be respectful when visiting. It's very moving and emotional.
Speaker 114: Actually, I think that's mislabeled. It's supposed to be Arlington.
In July, now she's in South
Speaker 43: Dakota. Watertown, South Dakota.
She did not like the
Speaker 5: hotel. They chose the hotel because of the deal. We chose this hotel because of
Speaker 21: the deal that was online. Now, after staying there, we can see why it was a deal.
The
Speaker 21: free breakfast in the morning was just your basic bagel cream cheese yogurt spread. The
only bonus
Speaker 21: about this hotel was that it was close to where we had to be for a wedding. The
beds were
Speaker 21: decent. Everything just seemed extremely dated, even though it just recently undergone a renovation.
While we were
Speaker 21: staying there, there
Speaker 115: was an early construction going on outside our door and the hotel rooms next to us, so don't plan on being able to sleep in.
I'll be
Speaker 116: honest. I don't fly in a Gulfstream five. I don't stay at the Ritz in Paris, but that looks
like a
Speaker 116: pretty normal hotel to me. It looks pretty nice. I mean,
Speaker 117: I'm a plebe. I'll admit it. I'm one of those people, you know, I
Speaker 118: don't, I don't stay at the Ritz. You're not going to catch me anywhere like that.
but
Speaker 45: apparently the Rum Coda Hotel and Watertown Event Center did not
Speaker 21: meet her expectations. Not
at all did it meet
Speaker 21: her expectations. So let's review here. September 2016, she registers ericalanemanagement.com and elm.groupdomains. January 2017, she forms Elm Group LLC, presumably means Erica Lane Management. And
then in March,
Speaker 58: she's in Italy.
Speaker 58: with her family, in Rome, Italy with her family, and then Florence, Siena, and Chianti with friends.
At the end of March into
Speaker 5: April, she's in Paris, France on business. April's 2017, she's in Santiago, Chile on business.
May of
Speaker 5: 2017, she's back in New York,
but she is for some reason
Speaker 58: staying in hotels. And
then in
Speaker 109: 2017, June of 2017, she's in Arlington, and
and we
Speaker 109: know she probably got there by Amtrak because it's her favorite way to get to D.C.,
and then she's back
Speaker 63 (lower-pitched voice): in New York City in June of 2017 and Arlington again in, excuse me, July of 2017, and back in Arlington again in July. So D.C., New York, D.C., New York, D.C., back and forth, back
Speaker 119: and forth, back and forth.
Guys, I
Speaker 119: don't know what
this
Speaker 120: means. I
don't know what this
Speaker 121: means.
I know where
Speaker 121: she was. I
know what
Speaker 61: she claims to have been doing. I
know she
Speaker 61: claims to have been conducting business in three different continents. I
Speaker 61: doesn't have a LinkedIn job or job listed on LinkedIn
Speaker 14: at that point. I know she's never told anybody where she worked at that
point. She just claims
Speaker 14: she worked for her nonprofit.
but the
Speaker 14: nonprofit never raised or spent more than $50,000. So how are
Speaker 122: you going to these places? Why would you be traveling to these places for that? So that
Speaker 61: doesn't make sense. I'm ruling out that this is nonprofit business. And
it really does
Speaker 61: raise the question of what the hell was she doing
there? And it
Speaker 49: plays into the ultimate questions, three, who killed Charlie Kirk? How did they do it and why?
because in
Speaker 14: the run-up to meeting him at Bill's Burgers for
a job
Speaker 123: interview-turned-date request, she's
traveling all over the world having business
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): meetings. She's
staying in hotels in the city
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): she supposedly lives in. Like, what is she
Speaker 61: doing? Who is this woman?
That's
Speaker 61: the question. Who is this woman? It's important because she is the presumed successor.
She is
Speaker 61: the one
Speaker 8: who was given over. So if she's working for Intel or she's working as a lady of the night, I don't think Charlie knew either
one of
Speaker 8: those. And
I'm having trouble
Speaker 8: coming up with a third explanation, to be honest with you. I don't have one.
And it's probably why we don't have
Speaker 8: an explanation of where she was working at the time.
Speaker 8: because she can't come up with a third one either. I
guess there's a third
Speaker 125: option. She's just a liar.
But I like to give
Speaker 125: people
Speaker 126 (lower-pitched voice): the benefit of the doubt. I
like to believe
Speaker 126 (lower-pitched voice): they're not liars. I like to believe they're spies or hookers.
Speaker 127: That's where I say, that's where my mind goes. I can't help it. I can't help it.
All
Speaker 5: right. I've got to play this clip. It's been everywhere today. And I would do myself a disservice
Speaker 88 (lower-pitched voice): not to comment on this because I have extremely, extremely strong feelings about this clip I'm about to play.
This man has
Speaker 88 (lower-pitched voice): crossed the
line to
Speaker 16: me, and he is now irredeemable. Not irredeemable. The Lord Jesus himself could redeem him, but no one else on earth can. And
you will never convince me
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): he's a good guy after this one minute and 15 second clip. You'll never convince me he's a good guy.
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): You'll never convince me he's leading a country that's the good country
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): after this one minute and 15 second clip.
Because you don't
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): say these things. When you're the leader of a country, you don't say these things about other religions. You don't say these things about the religious leaders of other religions.
Speaker 128: You just don't.
I don't care what
Speaker 128: you think about Hindus or Buddhists or Christians.
Muslims
Speaker 128: or Christians or Jews, you just don't comment on people's leaders like this, the leaders of
their religions, not
Speaker 18: when you are leading a country. I speak, of course, of the potentially AI version of Netanyahu. I want to play this, and I
Speaker 129: want you to listen carefully. I'll
put the, do I
Speaker 129: have closed captions here? I
don't know if I do
Speaker 130: or not.
I don't know how
Speaker 131: loud it is, so if it's quiet, I'll tell you what he says. He
Speaker 132: also wrote The Lessons
Speaker 131: of History, very brief, 100-page book,
in which
Speaker 133: he said, well, history proves that,
unfortunately and
Speaker 134 (lower-pitched voice): unhappily, Jesus Christ has no advantage over Julius Khan.
Jesus
Speaker 135: Christ has no advantage over Genghis Khan, Genghis Khan, or however you pronounce it.
Mr. Prime
Speaker 136: Minister, I
Speaker 126 (lower-pitched voice): disagree. I
totally 100%
Speaker 126 (lower-pitched voice): disagree. I'm
going to let him
Speaker 5: keep playing because it actually gets worse. I kind of thought after he played that,
I was
Speaker 5: like, oh, maybe he digs
himself out
Speaker 5: of this hole.
Because if
Speaker 133: you are strong enough,
Speaker 134 (lower-pitched voice): ruthless enough, powerful enough, evil will overcome good.
Yeah, we know
Speaker 126 (lower-pitched voice): that. We're watching you closely. We're well aware that evil can overcome good. You've proven it time and time again.
Aggression will
Speaker 137: overcome moderation.
So you have
Speaker 137: no choice. If
you look
Speaker 137: at the world as it is today,
you have to be
Speaker 134 (lower-pitched voice): blind not to see that the democracies led by the United States
are
Speaker 134 (lower-pitched voice): have to reassert their will to defend themselves and to oppose their enemies in time while there's still time, before the jarring gong of danger wakes them up and wakes them up too late. This is where we are now. The fact that people don't see that, the fact that a lot of the news media are harking on a lot of fake news, but
also a lot of...
A lot
Speaker 134 (lower-pitched voice): of short-sightedness and do not see the historic period and the historic struggle that we are engaged in now
doesn't obviate
Speaker 134 (lower-pitched voice): these truths. I'm
going to
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): summarize what he said. He
said, you Christians are
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): foolish following
Speaker 139: your God.
you
Speaker 140: Christians are foolish to follow your God. Instead, you need to be aggressive, ruthless, and evil. There
are Christian churches
Speaker 140: all over America, all over the world, who revere this guy and the country he leads. And
his message
Speaker 141: back to you is, you're a fool.
that's his
Speaker 78: message back to you,
that your God is
Speaker 78: helpless. Your God can't do, I mean, does he read the Old Testament? Does he read
the Tanakh, whatever they
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): call the Old Testament? Does he read it? Did he read how many times that they came
to the
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): Hebrews and said, your God is healing?
is
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): incompetent, he's weak, our God is better.
This was so disheartening and so
Speaker 128: disappointing because I know what's going to happen this Sunday
and I know what's
Speaker 128: going to happen next Sunday on Easter and I know what's going to happen the Sunday after
Speaker 142: that.
Churches all
Speaker 16: over the world are going to gather and they're going to have this flag hanging in their auditorium and they're going to have this flag played up on a screen and people will be, whoo, it's demonic.
It's
Speaker 143 (lower-pitched voice): just demonic. I'm sorry.
The man
Speaker 143 (lower-pitched voice): just denigrated your God.
He just
Speaker 143 (lower-pitched voice): said your God has
no power
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): over Genghis Khan, meaning Genghis Khan
is evil
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): and vicious and he attacks
and your God
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): is helpless against him.
That assumes a
Speaker 144: very, very, Thank you.
Speaker 143 (lower-pitched voice): temporal view of the world. It discounts the eternal. It discounts the entire Christian
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): gospel. And any church who goes and now slobbers all over this guy this weekend, any
Christian group
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): that holds
this guy
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): or his country up as a model of
Speaker 116: somebody we should be dying
for has to
Speaker 116: own that line.
Speaker 44: They have to own that line.
they have
Speaker 1: to own the line that Jesus Christ is not powerful enough, that he has no power over these people, that he has no power over evil.
Speaker 145: Sir, this is why we disagree with your methods of fighting wars. This is why we disagree with your method of just
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): removing entire populations from near you
and mowing
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): over their homes and their businesses and their hospitals and their churches and their schools and their synagogues and their mosques and everything in its way.
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): This is why we disapprove
Speaker 139: of those tactics, because we don't believe in a God who's weaker than evil. We
believe our reward is
Speaker 139: eternal, sir.
We believe if
Speaker 1: we follow
the good
Speaker 1: here and we pledge our allegiance to the right guy, then our
Speaker 128: reward is eternal.
I'm
Speaker 128: oversimplifying the gospel, certainly. You guys understand that.
But the
Speaker 44: message of Christianity is not annihilate your neighbors before they annihilate you. That's not the message. That's
not the
Speaker 44: message of Christianity. The message of Christianity is not
In
Speaker 44: order to annihilate your neighbors, make sure they could never
Speaker 5: inhabit the area again. Knock down every house, knock down every hospital, knock down every school, knock down every place of worship, knock down every road, every bridge, knock down every gas station, knock down every fuel line, knock down every water source,
Speaker 44: starve the people. That's not the message of Christianity. We're fundamentally different. This has been my point
Speaker 74: this whole time.
This is why I don't
Speaker 74: support your actions, sir. Your actions are not Christian. They don't line up with our faith.
They
Speaker 74: are anti-Christian, so to speak.
Anyone who
Speaker 74: then
Speaker 8: advocates for that would be an anti-Christ. I
think you're looking at him. It is
Speaker 8: demonic.
Speaker 82 (higher-pitched voice): There is no Christian way to look at that statement and say, well, here's what he really meant. No, no.
There is
Speaker 82 (higher-pitched voice): no Christian way to evaluate what he said and come
out with
Speaker 82 (higher-pitched voice): a good answer. It doesn't exist. It doesn't exist.
Speaker 146: Christians will follow people like this to the gates of hell and then they'll be let in
that's that's that's
Speaker 1: where
Speaker 61: this leads he's giving the game away sometimes the demons that control people can't help themselves they say too much and
I believe in
Speaker 61: that he's led by demons
no
Speaker 1: Christian could do to other populations what he's doing. None, none, nor should they support it.
It's not who we
Speaker 140: are. We
don't teach them because
Speaker 140: they're Christian. We teach them because we're Christian.
That is the most
Speaker 147: satanic comment I've ever heard come out of a world leader's
mouth.
Speaker 148: Period.
It just is. Even the
Speaker 1: leaders who supposedly say death to Israel, death to America, they're not calling Jesus powerless over evil. They're
Speaker 85: not. They're not. They're not saying that. You're saying that.
i don't know how any christian can
Speaker 150: continue to support this after
that line i
Speaker 150: don't
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): know how they could have supported it up until today but after today you got to pick a side you've got to pick a side and
if your local
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): politician supports this you've got to pick a side it's it's your soul guys at this point it's your soul
If you
Speaker 151: vote for somebody who supports that, it's your soul. I believe that. I
don't think you can recover from a statement. I think
Speaker 140: the only way is to bend your knee
on the day of
Speaker 140: judgment and beg for mercy.
And I suppose, as a
Speaker 152: Christian, we're supposed to pray that they all get that opportunity.
but
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): I mean, I was devastated when I saw that because I, because I know, I know people who love this guy and I love, love what the country over there is doing. Well, that's what they're doing.
That's what he
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): just gave the game away.
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): That's what they're doing.
That's what
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): they're doing.
You can support
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): it as your will. You
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): can support it, but you're going to have to answer for that one. You're
going to
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): have to answer one day. I support a guy who said this, and
Speaker 1: let me
tell you DJT
Speaker 1: supporters.
You
Speaker 1: remember when he was on an airport, Donald Trump, and said, I don't think
Speaker 44: I'm going to heaven? He didn't say, I don't believe in heaven, and I think that's a myth. I could have at least understood that if he said, you know, I'm 80. As I look out at the world, I'm in big boy politics now. I see what's going on behind the scenes. I don't even know that I believe in heaven anymore. Okay, at least I'll give you a pass there. You're not making a conscious decision to reject it. You just haven't gotten there yet.
no he
Speaker 50 (higher-pitched voice): said i don't think i'm going to heaven as if i know it exists and i know what's required of me to get there and i'm not willing to do it i'd rather go to hell i mean that's basically what he said if you say i don't think i'm going to heaven that means i'm choosing not to i agree it exists and i'm choosing not to go i think he's been hanging around this guy too many
Speaker 77 (higher-pitched voice): times
i think for the sake
Speaker 77 (higher-pitched voice): of his soul he needs to get away from a guy like this
I'm
Speaker 8: sorry, I am so fed up with what's going on right now.
I am so fed
Speaker 8: up with it.
I don't want to
Speaker 63 (lower-pitched voice): say too much more because I'll get myself in trouble. But
I am
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): just, I
will
Speaker 16: never vote for anyone else that supports this.
not
Speaker 16: for dog catcher, not for president, no office,
Speaker 116: no office. You can say, I don't care. That's not my
Speaker 1: issue. All right, I'll give you a pass.
But if you say
Speaker 1: I support that, I'll
either sit it out or vote for
Speaker 1: the other
Speaker 16: guy.
If it's a primary, I'll vote
Speaker 16: for the other guy. If it's not, I'll sit it out. I'm not voting for these
guys. I'm
Speaker 16: just not.
I will
Speaker 16: not reward somebody who
Speaker 126 (lower-pitched voice): denigrates Christ. And he did. And
if you
Speaker 126 (lower-pitched voice): support him, you are. Period. There's
no other way to
Speaker 139: look at it.
Just to be
Speaker 139: clear, Jesus
does
Speaker 128: have power over Genghis Khan. And you, sir, he has power over you.
Because one
Speaker 128: day you're going to have to
Speaker 128: Account for every one of those buildings that's been knocked down, every home destroyed, every school that's been knocked down, every little kid that's been killed, every innocent civilian that's been killed. You're going to have to account for that.
And I don't want to be around when
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): it happens. I hope you get there before me and you're long ahead of the
line and
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): I don't have to watch it.
I
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): hope I get
in
Speaker 63 (lower-pitched voice): line behind the little girls who got bombed. That's who I hope I get in line behind.
I think that'll be a different
Speaker 156: conversation.
Speaker 157: I
think that'll be a totally
Speaker 157: different conversation.
all
Speaker 158: right at the risk of saying too much i'm gonna pull
that down lest i
Speaker 159: get too
out of
Speaker 159: control all right
Speaker 3: let me pull up some of your comments here guys i appreciate you joining me early today this has been earlier than normal um we'll uh we'll get a really good
Speaker 16: night's sleep as a community as a as a family here as a family you know how we do it a family
We
Speaker 16: may not know tonight, we may not know what Erica was doing during that period of 2017, but we know she was doing something that involved
Speaker 11: business at
hotels in
Speaker 11: Paris, multiple hotels in Santiago, Chile, and hotels in a city in which she lived.
We know that. We know that. That's how much we've advanced the
Speaker 160: ball down the
Speaker 1: road.
It
Speaker 161: gets us every little piece gets us there. I know people get frustrated and say, why are you talking about her? You
need to
Speaker 161: go back to the scene of the crime. We did. We went back to the basics.
But I think
Speaker 161: this is all
Speaker 61: important. So we'll spend some shows talking about her as well.
It was a, I was a longtime
Speaker 61: listener of the CK show. I have never had a good vibe about
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): AK. Always hated when he was on. Always felt he added nothing to the show. And he always seemed like a phony to me. He's proven me correct.
TB, EK,
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): AK, all CK's handlers.
I'm
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): starting to really come to your position on Andrew Colbert, to be honest with you. I'm
starting to really come around to
Speaker 162: your position. I'm starting to be convinced that he's
not an
Speaker 162: incidental player.
Thank you
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): for that.
The gold glitter
Speaker 16: hoodie. We all know you bought it.
We all
Speaker 163: saw your
Speaker 16: eyes light up. Yeah, well, I might surprise you in
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): it one day. It might
be a
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): good members
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): get up.
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): Thank you,
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): Well, we got to stop making fun of him for being old because now he's officially old.
Just
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): checking in. How's the social security paperwork going?
Did you get the
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): walker I sent with tennis balls? The tennis balls.
Blink help if
Speaker 18: Morse code if the nurses aren't changing the bedpads. All right. I got it. I'm old. Duly noted. Do
you think CK
Speaker 18: figured out EK's betrayal? Um...
I think he
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): probably wondered why she wasn't coming to his side as he was changing. Any
ideas how many
Speaker 169 (lower-pitched voice): times you say Joe and the great Joe crash out? I had to count because it makes me laugh. 39 times, Baron. Poor Joe. Did I say
Speaker 170: it 39 times? I would have guessed like 15. 39? One
for each of her
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): IQ points. I asked
you for something to
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): research a while ago. That same night, I fell and fractured my skull.
We had a
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): microburst while watching you a couple weeks later. Currently
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): covered in bubble wrap. Oh, my gosh. I didn't
know you could
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): fracture your skull. I
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): guess you can. It's a bone, but I've not heard of people doing that. I'm
sorry to hear
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): that. I hope you're doing better. It was a while ago, I guess. I love
you,
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): brother. Please pray for us in the UK after changes to full-term abortion laws. Our nation has been sold to the devil. Christ is king. Christ is
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): king indeed. You have. You
have. You have.
Anyone
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): who will abort a nine-month-old baby is sick.
Anyone who will
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): support that is sick. Barron, first-time Super Chat, long-time listener. Just wanted to say I love your
Speaker 44: passion, humor, intellect, and Popeye laugh.
Popeye
Speaker 85: laugh? Huh? I
don't even know
Speaker 85: how he laughs.
Didn't he say yam, yam, yam
Speaker 170: or something? Yuck, yuck, yuck? I
don't know. Go,
Speaker 170: Max. I'll
do my
Speaker 170: best.
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): I'll do my best.
Thank you
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): for going early. I've been missing lives with my new work schedule. God bless. Oh, you're welcome.
Hit the like
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): button, y'all. Love you, Barron. Thank you for all you and Daisy do. Yeah, Daisy was a massive help to today's show. She's always a help, but today was especially
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): helpful. Thank
you guys for
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): hitting the like button. It's awfully helpful. We're trying to overcome a little
Speaker 174: algorithmic jail here. I'm not sure my rants are helping, but since they're not pushing it out, I might as well go on my rants.
Speaker 36: Oh.
But Joe Kent, I get why he
Speaker 36: resigned. Here, let
me make
Speaker 36: this a little bigger. But
is it better to
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): leave and make a statement or stay to try and make a change? What
if the
Speaker 141: successor is worse? The successor assuredly
will be
Speaker 141: worse. But I mean,
I don't
Speaker 175: know. That's a good question. I'm not sure the answer to it.
Most of Jonestown did not drink
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): the Kool-Aid voluntarily. Those who wouldn't drink were shot. Some of them were shot
and some
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): of them were
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): injected,
Speaker 176: actually.
Speaker 18: YouTube won't let me praise the politician that resigned yesterday, no matter how worded he is a hero, hope this worked, it did it did, and I agree
with you Baron definitely
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): getting throttled when waiting for you to start likes were
Speaker 177: above 310, now two minutes in stuck at 258, everyone check your likes wow, go back and look at your likes yeah, they're mad at me for
a
Speaker 178: couple things I did I
can't help I'm
Speaker 180: gonna be me
they'll get
Speaker 159: over it at some point.
I've talked
Speaker 159: to people who have had this happen to them, and they say likes is the best way to
overcome it. Because
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): likes kind of reset it. Well, they don't, they don't, they're not throttling you. They just take away all the advantages you have built into your channel. So as you build up likes and comments and airtime
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): and watch time and all that, your algorithm sort of climbs. And then when they get mad at you, they start
Speaker 143 (lower-pitched voice): it back over. And so you have to basically build it back up over weeks, months, whatever. But we're having fun.
We're having fun.
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): Please look into the family of international children
of God
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): cult embedded in D.C. for decades. Invisible, influencing DJT. EK teamed up with in Romania. Programmed EK, part of Calvary Chapel. EK said, family,
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): is this her religion? Those are all good questions. I anticipate more on that soon based on conversations I've had behind
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): the scenes. So, stand by. Stand by. Wow,
YouTube is
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): simpering Super Chats big time tonight. Go, Max. Yeah, they're mad. They big mad. Love you,
Speaker 75: man. Go, Max.
love
Speaker 75: you too will do
uh whoop
Speaker 75: whoop love you all
uh thank
Speaker 75: you thank
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): you veronica
baron thank you for inspiring people to
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): do better and be better you keep history honest when others
try to rewrite
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): it please carry naloxone
uh my
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): sister carries it
i guess i should i
Speaker 183: mean i don't know
i think i'm around
Speaker 183: anybody
Speaker 184: who does that stuff uh i don't know mrs coleman she's
in and
Speaker 184: out who knows what she
no i
Speaker 184: don't think she does that either
Speaker 184: can you
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): just order it on Amazon or I
got to
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): go in somewhere because I don't want to go in ordering stuff that looks like I'm a drug addict that's how that's how
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): rumors get started
Speaker 185: love
the
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): red B oh thank you this is my
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): angry red I was a little angry after I saw that video Erica's programmed to be whoever they want whenever they want all the way up to VP
of the country
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): she's completely controllable
don't disagree
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): with you
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): Thank you for reminding us about liking the show. I always forget. I will do my best. I'll do better. I often forget myself. Jesus Christ, the way, the truth, and the light. Praise Jesus. It was lost, but turned to him, and
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): he has turned to me. God bless. Christ is king. God is good. Christ is king indeed. Thank you.
Speaker 187: Woo-hoo. One month. I went down a Jim Jones rabbit hole a few years ago. What happened in Guyana is so dark. Go
Max
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): Barron. I left out a lot of facts because there are some disputed facts, and I only wanted to include facts that are really not disputed at all.
So a lot of
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): the recordings are disputed because people say they could have
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): been edited or stuff could have been removed or whatever. I've listened to dozens of hours. I don't want to say hundreds because I don't think
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): it's true, but dozens of hours of the recordings. They're available publicly. I think the University of San Diego may have them all or someone down there.
Maybe San
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): Diego State, some California, Southern California University.
Speaker 18: But there are a lot of really interesting facts about how long it took authorities to get in. And when they finally got in, the bodies had all been moved.
Speaker 18: which means
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): someone else was there ahead of time and there were tire tracks and as if maybe an intelligence operation came in, moved stuff around, maybe finished off some survivors,
including the
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): leader. There was also recordings of people saying we need to call the CIA. We need to get out of here
as if
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): they thought that was an option.
So it's an
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): interesting rabbit hole to go down, but some of that's disputed
and I
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): did not want to include anything in the opening that I felt like had much dispute to it.
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, I screwed up the website yesterday. Because I'm not preparing a show tomorrow, all day tomorrow and all day
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): Saturday, I am going to get it fixed. I am going to commit to getting it fixed, but I was not able to do it today. This
Speaker 189: show took a little prep. But
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): Barron, by the way, Daisy was mentioned yesterday's show on CK's
show by
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): Blake. They laughed saying she needs to research the Corey Ritchie's case around the
Speaker 190: 23-minute mark. Go, Max. Daisy? Daisy?
Speaker 190: Daisy, you're famous.
You have to
Speaker 191: watch this show pretty closely to know Daisy.
Hi, guys. Will
Speaker 82 (higher-pitched voice): you email me and tell me where she worked in 2017, please? Andrew, Blake, Mikey. I know
Speaker 145: you're amazing. You got
Speaker 64: to know, Mikey. You got to know. I know you were like four when she was working in 2017, but you can ask. You can ask. That's interesting, though. I will, uh,
I
Speaker 64: did research the Corey Ritchie's case a little bit. It's interesting they would tell us to research it because Corey Ritchie's, if you watch Candace talk about it, she did an okay job talking about it. But this woman was like a hero.
This woman
Speaker 64: was the grieving widow that
Speaker 192: everybody gave a free pass because her husband died.
And it turned out
Speaker 193: she killed her husband.
So, I
Speaker 193: mean, like,
interesting you would tell
Speaker 194: her to research that, guys.
Maybe
Speaker 195: they're trying to crack the case.
Speaking
Speaker 195: of demons, like Jim Jones, did you finish
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): Sean Ryan's pod with Father Ripperger? I
was Ray
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): Baptist, but I'm thinking of converting insanely powerful. I did. He does a great job. Roll that beautiful bean footage. If you're looking for other similar content, there's something on Spotify called The Exorcist Files. Go
back
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): to season one, episode one. Start
from the
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): beginning. You'll be enthralled. If you liked what he had to say, you're going to love Father Carlos Martins. Very similar styles.
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, very similar
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): beliefs, um, and, uh, very similar presentation styles. Father Carlos Martins does these kind
of
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): acts them out though. And they're really good. Really good. If you like that, you'll love that.
Uh, I replied on one of your
Speaker 197: tweets yesterday about people drinking the Kool-Aid. Tell me that inspired this great opening statement. I'd be proud. Um, if
Speaker 16: that was you, it did because, um, that's where
I got
Speaker 16: the ideas.
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): I was, I was on X yesterday. I have a whole long list of, of openings I want to do. And it was...
Jim
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): Jones was on that opening and on the list,
but I wasn't
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): sure the approach
I wanted to
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): take, but then, you know,
with
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): the South America connection, with the Intel operation connection, with, with the taking
over a huge
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): operation
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): and then literally running it into the ground and destroying it. I
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): thought, man, this is just too many parallels here. I got to,
I got to
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): do it in this context. So yeah, it,
I
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): mean, I don't know how many people did. I
only
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): saw one reference, so it could have been you.
TPUSA's
Speaker 16: extension, Jim Jones. Glad you're awake. Very awake, sir. Very awake.
Everybody needs to read
Speaker 116: Chaos by Tom O'Neill. Agreed. I read that book probably five years ago.
Maybe longer than that. Maybe
Speaker 116: six or
Speaker 18: seven years ago, because I know where I lived when I read it.
It was great. It
Speaker 18: was phenomenal.
Checked it out
Speaker 18: of the local library,
Speaker 198: so I didn't...
didn't
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): burn up any of the family money reading a for fun book, but it was fantastic. It was absolutely wonderful. If you've not read it, guy took
Speaker 169 (lower-pitched voice): years to write the book chaos by Tom O'Neill, all about the CIA military experience and mind control. So I'm not surprised that Jonestown deaths were MK as well. I remember it. Well, horrible. Yeah, I agree
with
Speaker 16: you. Hey, Baron, excellent open as always just checking in to ask if you remember to get your package from FedEx pickup point.
It's been
Speaker 16: two weeks since
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): it arrived there. Keep going, Max. No, I did not. I'm glad you just said that. I need to get
over
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): there. But luckily, tomorrow and Saturday, I have time. So thank you.
Happy to catch you
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): live today. Appreciate your vigilance on the
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): CK situation. Thank you. I'm glad you were able to catch you live. Maybe I'll do some more early shows here and there. I was 12 when Jonestown happened. Life magazine had an amazing and disturbing photos of piles of bodies. Yeah, I've seen them all.
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): I've seen as many as I know exist. Cults are happening all the time. Some are huge, some are small, but they're all around us. Sadly, they don't seem to go away. Yeah, but I'm talking about like the heyday of cults. The cults that were in the
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): public consciousness that we all knew about.
That seems to
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): have kind of gone.
My family's
Speaker 169 (lower-pitched voice): from Guyana. They remember that tragedy like yesterday. My grandfather worked the gold mines during that time.
Always love
Speaker 169 (lower-pitched voice): your openings. Thank you. Thank you.
By the way,
Speaker 169 (lower-pitched voice): thanks for all you do. I was born into
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): a Catholic church.
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): gam and
uncle even a
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): priest oh fam probably yeah the
f and g
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): right next to each other i've been away from church for years several weeks
ago i went
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): to mass
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): but last night came back to christ during your show well thank you
that is unbelievable um i
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): love hearing stories like that i love that you guys feel comfortable enough to share your victories your setbacks your pains it's not just with me but with the with the chat during the show
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): it truly has
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): become a really special community. So
thank you
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): for sharing. Cabot's dad, on deeper search,
graduated
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): with Russian studies at the university level. Seems most of his past wiped from the internet. For Cabot, no internet presence at all until college. All sus.
All in
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): the family, for espionage, that is, in my humble opinion. His
dad
Speaker 200: ran, what
was the name
Speaker 201: of the company his dad ran? I had several friends that worked for them. I
can't think
Speaker 202: of the name of it.
It was
Speaker 202: a big ground game operation, similar to what TPUSA is doing now. AFP,
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): Americans for Prosperity.
And
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): that was a wild organization back in its day.
Most appropriate
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): streamer
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): substitute on the day's Candice is attending other missions. You guys have really helped me keep my thoughts in. Oh,
thank you. I'm glad
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): I'm your substitute teacher. She is the principal.
Dan
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): Flugg regularly recorded on his glasses at TP College events, so they were just studying human behavior, searching for patsies, or stealing biometric data on young military age men. I don't know why you would.
Do you believe in
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): angels on Earth? Yes, I believe
angels can come
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): to Earth and
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): interact with us, or not, but just be present. Yes, I do.
massey
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): is a widower too so people should stop attacking him accusing him of being involved in first
wife's death they
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): should he has
the
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): widower's exception along with erica kirk and joe kent immune from criticism thank
you for
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): leaving hypothetical aunt sue out of things lately
you put that poor
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): fake woman through so much in the past for cultivating such a great
Speaker 203 (lower-pitched voice): community like the vid share on social media
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): yeah sharing helps um
So
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): liking is a tremendous part
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): of the algorithm, but sharing also helps quite a bit. And subscriptions, obviously. And watch time. That's like it.
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): It's a mathematical formula. You see Nissy video about story written about Erica and Charlie. They listed a second last name for her mural. I did see that story.
At
Speaker 204: first, I didn't think it was legit until her ELM company surfaced. Thoughts? Ooh, that's interesting. That's interesting.
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): interesting i always thought it was erica lane management because that was the website i don't know i'm kind of going with erica lane management
because that was
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): the website she opened right before she opened
elm group baron
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): massey follows you on x member show um i could do a member show um i've not looked at my followers i don't know who follows me but thank you for
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): sharing that that's interesting
uh does
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): he have like a zillion i mean does he follow a zillion people
I'll
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): look him up.
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): I'll look him up.
I'll follow
Speaker 46: him back. Yeah, he follows 25,000 people. I
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): don't think I'm
going to pop
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): up in his feed anytime soon.
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): Hey, bye, baby. Thank
you for
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): sharing that. How
do we
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): know it was her in any pic? No friends, none of just of
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): her. Total fake trips, IMHO.
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): Well, Daisy so astutely pointed out during the program that some pics
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): are hers and some of the screenshots are not. So, but you can go, if you go to her profile, you can see the
Speaker 203 (lower-pitched voice): thumbnails and look at her reviews. And if she's attached a pic, you can find those as well. So
you can
Speaker 203 (lower-pitched voice): fact
Speaker 206: check. You can fact check it all. Great. Now you have all the women in the chat talking about YouTube's censored word. Thanks.
Speaker 208: Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Are they talking about Wayne?
They're talking
Speaker 208: about David. David's box. David's little
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): black box.
Are
Speaker 209: they talking about his little Macron? It's
EID
Speaker 210: tomorrow. Busy prepping the house. Listening to B-B-B-Baron in my high IQ outfit.
Love
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): your show. First ever membership. I EID. I don't know what that means. Is
that a
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): religious holiday?
I'm looking it
Speaker 211: up. I'm looking it up.
Speaker 211: P-I-D-B-U-B-B-R-A-K.
Blessed
Speaker 212 (lower-pitched voice): Festival, tradition of Muslim greeting used during the Eid al-Fitr celebration.
Oh, the end of
Speaker 166: Ramadan. So you people could eat again. I'll tell you what,
that's
Speaker 213: commitment. We
just not allowed to eat
Speaker 213: fish on Friday, and that's hard enough.
Speaker 116: I mean, we're not allowed to eat meat on Friday,
and I
Speaker 116: start panicking.
I
Speaker 116: really want to ask the bishop for dispensation
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): Because I don't eat wheat, I don't eat dairy I don't eat eggs If you tell me I can't eat meat, what's left? I have
Speaker 49: to pig out on mercury And lead infested fish With PCBs in it or whatever Well, happy holidays to you XO Rivers
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): OX
Love the
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): reference to Carmen Sandiego Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes That was a favorite of mine growing
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): up
When I
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): was a little tiny kid
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, closed captions are not available on your latest vid. I usually download the transcript so I can look up keywords and get timestamps. Could you possibly check yesterday's video and toggle CC on?
Speaker 214: Yeah.
Is it not
Speaker 215: on? Details.
Speaker 216: Hmm.
they're
Speaker 217: on subtitles no restrictions
Speaker 218: oh no it's not the
auto not
Speaker 218: on it's asking me if I want to upload subtitles I
Speaker 219: wonder why
Speaker 218: oh
it
Speaker 220: says English
has been published I'll look at it
Speaker 142: again complete
I don't
Speaker 142: want to take too much time on it right now, but I'll look at it again.
Quality show
Speaker 221: again, man. What do you make of prosecution telling Judge Graff in the March
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): 13th hearing that they still await the ATF's full case
Speaker 222: file and preliminary forensic bed evidence materials? Um...
I
Speaker 223: don't make anything of it.
I don't
Speaker 223: make anything of it. I mean, just being conscientious and making sure you have all the information. I don't make anything nefarious of it, if that's what you're asking.
I'd love to
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): see a photo of the real Rosa Parks behind you, Barron. Please look into that story. The photo on your wall portrays a paid actress.
For
Speaker 224: real?
look
Speaker 224: up Jehovah's Witnesses and mind control technique. You guys are blowing my
Speaker 225 (higher-pitched voice): mind tonight. Back-to-back texts. First, Rose is not real, and now Jehovah's Witnesses are mind controllers? I know
that I'm
Speaker 225 (higher-pitched voice): going to survive this podcast.
Speaker 116: Uh, why are cults like Jonestown and FLDS all involved in the church of Zion?
Speaker 226 (lower-pitched voice): Is it the same Zion FLDS located around AZ, UT, DNV, ND, same as Egyptian planes, same cities, missing kids, child brides. And I don't know.
Speaker 227: You're blowing my mind here. I had no idea that was true. I'll
confess
Speaker 228: ignorance. I don't know what FLDS is. I
know what
Speaker 228: LDS is, but I don't think they do polygamy anymore.
Um, and
Speaker 195: I, I don't, yeah, I don't know.
I'm
Speaker 195: happy to look into it. Barron, I don't speak Italian, but
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): yours is flawless.
You put your mind
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): to it. My mom was right. If you put your mind to it, you can't do anything.
All you got to do
Speaker 36: is this, and you can speak Italian, too. Not talking like it is. I
mean, you're
Speaker 18: good. What's your name? B-H-H-O-D-G. Put a little
E at
Speaker 18: the end. You're good. Wow, Daisy, this
type
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): of diggings are absolutely impressive
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): and amazing. Well done, and thank you, too.
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): uh yeah she's a goat no doubt about it thank you for that generosity by the way i'll never forget how terrified i was as a
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): sixth grader when i found out about jim jones his cult his kool-aid and all those dead people who gave their
own kids
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): poison
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): before imbibing it themselves yeah
that's the myth
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): though they didn't all that's
what i'm
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): saying they they portrayed it as
if it was
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): this big happy fun event and then that's not the truth watch valhalla latest and Arenas built
a
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): big no bueno.
Trump
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): has successfully made the yuan, the currency for petroleum.
This has dire
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): consequences for the U.S. If you were on my member show last week, you know this is what I warned of.
That this
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): was my biggest fear and my biggest holdback with any action over there.
Barron, have you
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): caught Wolves and Finance's video regarding the close-range shooter wearing a tan?
Wearing tan. Compelling
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): theory, and I love your take. Shout out to Cassia, Daily Fritto, CCCO, and
Speaker 230: Lionel. Love the collapse.
Speaker 230: I've spoken a lot about the guy in tan and it's not a palm gun. I mean, it's just not.
If someone
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): brings me evidence that it's a palm gun beyond just he pulled on his sleeve at the exact same time,
but I'd like to see
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): somebody make that shot. I'd like to see somebody make that shot with two people they know standing in the line of fire behind the target. I'd
like to see
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): somebody make that shot when there are real consequences. If they miss like,
like
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): you die or something like if you don't hit the shot
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): you die um i mean it's got it's that's not a palm gun so i don't know why he went down that road
um wolves
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): wolves is good when he's on
finance when he
Speaker 232: gets to global politics and uh and the mechanics of of the the big bang he's he waivers a little bit hey hey
i stayed at
Speaker 233: the ritz before it's definitely worth it though
i've never stayed at a ritz
Speaker 233: baby it's great
I would
Speaker 234: never pay that much for a hotel. It
would
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): be interesting to compare Egyptian airplanes with her trip. Thank you for your high IQ coverage. Crisis King. Crisis King, indeed.
I don't think you'll be
Speaker 236: able to find any records going back then.
The Ritz
Speaker 236: Hotel, she traveled as a couple, not on
Speaker 237: business anymore.
Maybe it was couple business. I
Speaker 237: don't know. Hey,
Siri, when
Speaker 237: was Emmanuel Macron elected?
Good
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): question.
Emanuel
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): Macron election.
That's
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): 2022. It was 2017, wasn't it? 2017 Emanuel
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): Macron election.
Speaker 240: Yeah. Oh. Oh.
Speaker 241: April of 2017. When
did Chile have
Speaker 242: an election that year? They
did.
Speaker 244: new rabbit hole to go down ladies and gentlemen holy mackerel next
you're going to tell me
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): there was an italian election at the same time i mean surely not almost you can't go you can't go three for three and she wasn't
Speaker 245: even there on business uh 20 but we'll look the 2017 italian election
April
Speaker 246: 30th, 2017.
Now
Speaker 247: you've ruined my weekend. I got to run that rabbit hole down. Great.
What if they had a
Speaker 248: firework show for who's you? I
Speaker 249: doubt it. I
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): doubt it.
was
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): studying for the CA bar exam when she was feeding knuckles in Europe. If she wasn't a murderous fraud, she
could be
Speaker 250: something. What a total waste said.
I don't
Speaker 251: think she sat for the California bar, did she? She sat for the New York real estate exam, but that was the year later.
Harris, the
Speaker 251: Ritz, travel as a couple.
There's a couple
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): business.
One
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): TripAdvisor affiliate program is the, this is the most common real way to make money. Creators, bloggers, and social media influencers sign up for the official program and post on socials. But she
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): wasn't posting it on the socials. She was just commenting, like leaving reviews. Thank you. And thank you.
It's not clear
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): why we're going through her
Speaker 3: travels post by post.
Hope you caught
Speaker 3: up. Do
you think that
Speaker 3: Dan Bongino is still working for the FBI? And do you think Joe Kent might be at risk of danger? Great opening statement.
Speaker 3: uh no
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): yes thank
you um i
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): didn't mean to be
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): so so trite on that but because we nobody knows where she was during that time period
and
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): now we do and it's saying she's working all over the world if that doesn't excite you i can't help i can't help that it excited me
did a google
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): search found
Speaker 252: nothing. Maybe Daisy can dive deeper. Did Lamar Odom have a connection with JT?
Speaker 252: Maybe that's how she knew Ye through the Kardashians. JT and Lamar both played for Oklahoma team.
Far more
Speaker 253: likely she would have known Lamar Odom through Harrelson,
Speaker 254: right?
Josh
Speaker 116: Harrelson. Was he JT also?
Speaker 255: Um...
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): was his uh he was josh harold josh douglas so that wasn't jt jt was the the baseball player oh you're saying he was playing in tulsa but that yeah i don't think
i don't think
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): he would have run into that guy uh i'm curious because
Speaker 256: harrelson played on the knicks in the heat was odom on either of those teams is that you're onto something here you might be onto
something let's
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): look here
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): when was he on those teams? Uh, he was on the clip. He was on the heat. No three Oh four.
Speaker 257: Um,
Speaker 258: Oh, so that was way different.
Speaker 259 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah. He was playing overseas in the Euro league by the time Harrelson was playing. So I
Speaker 260: don't, I don't know if that's a connection. I'm not sure what it is.
Good catch
Speaker 75: though. Good call.
I
Speaker 75: forgot Lamar Odom hung around with those people. Those knuckles aren't gluten-free, just saying.
Yeah, it'd be a lot of
Speaker 261: rice. I don't know. Maybe she likes rice. My
accents are
Speaker 261: on point.
Speaker 99: Finally, somebody who gets me. Finally. Thank
you for
Speaker 99: that.
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): A very generous contribution. No single 28-year-old has this kind of money when you're broke. She's
living in
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): one of the most expensive cities in the world.
So was
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): she dating CK already and still went on that reality show
something
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): else? I
don't want to make
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): too much of the reality show appearance.
She
Speaker 49: was a hanger on. Her roommate, the Sydney gal, she was on the show.
They just included
Speaker 49: Erica as like
Speaker 250: someone who went along
with Sydney
Speaker 250: as she went to some party or something. She wasn't on the show.
She was
Speaker 250: like,
Speaker 195: background.
Super chat is to bribe you
Speaker 195: into never speak an Italian again.
i
Speaker 262: speak
Speaker 263: ferrari
i'll allow it
Speaker 264: i'll allow it uh i'll allow it i don't think she visited
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): any of those places she's just setting herself up for when anyone wants to research her and then think highly of her she wants to look culturally well-rounded
why has no one found it yet i mean if
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): that was the case
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): wouldn't she be like accidentally dropped like putting it on her twitter profile or something
Speaker 145: no daisy's a goat if daisy hadn't found it nobody would have found it candace didn't know where she was didn't know what the elm group
was i'm just saying a travel agent
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): familiarized trip i think
she was a
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): travel agent what's she doing
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): all the meetings for then
all the
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): hotel business meetings
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): sound like a good cover to recruit girls that's kind of what I was hinting at.
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): either that or she
Speaker 75: was the girl, one or the other, or, or Intel, one or the other, I get other, or she's lying. Santiago wasn't there an orphanage there or South America somewhere. I
don't remember. I
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): know there was one in Haco, Costa Rica, but that's not South America. That's
Speaker 122: good. Good chunk of real estate between is people watching a euphemism for scouting girls. Now we're cooking with Greece.
She didn't say how old
Speaker 122: the people she was watching
Speaker 267: happened to be.
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, EFA, someone should definitely not tell her about those web history cleaning services.
Oh, oh, I'm sure she's hired him. Someone checked those
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): locations she was at in 2017 to see if Einstein, his people were there too.
Yeah, someone needs to run
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): those locations through the
Speaker 66: files. I'll
never trust
Speaker 66: TripAdvisor again. Crisis King, crisis King indeed. I mean, her reviews seem pretty thorough.
I don't
Speaker 66: think they were wrong.
Speaker 66: There is no rooftop at the Hilton Garden Inn in Santiago, Chile. FYI,
thank you
Speaker 66: for all your work. There might have been
Speaker 36: in 2017.
Hotels move around. Was
Speaker 36: Erika doing casting in Paris and Chile? Could that be, could
be that
Speaker 36: they invite candidates to the hotel to meet for an interview? She
claimed at some
Speaker 161: point to be a casting agent.
Speaker 268: What if it's a kidnapping agent? I
shouldn't have said that. I don't
Speaker 269: know. That's allegedly my opinion, maybe something to think about.
thank
Speaker 269: you for
Speaker 189: your contribution did
Speaker 195: you see those video of bb's walk with ambassador huckster and notice his ear has two canals can't think of any other reason for all those ai videos other than to hide his death what
say you i thought
Speaker 116: of another reason i said it in yesterday's
show i
Speaker 116: think it would be hilarious if
Speaker 54: they're just duping everybody
like he's alive and they
Speaker 54: know that people think he's dead so they're releasing
ai videos
Speaker 54: just to troll the world i think that would be hilarious in fact that's what i would
Speaker 213: do
Speaker 213: If I was
a diabolical
Speaker 213: Antichrist.
Speaker 270: That's how I
would
Speaker 213: play the game. Y'all would never know. I would never know. Loving some mint daddy
Speaker 18: crew.
Leaving some mint
Speaker 18: daddy crew.
Speaker 271: Yeah. I had a mint
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): daddy bun. Conference of the hotels on those dates, businesses. Yeah, Daisy, maybe we ought to look up on those dates if there are...
any
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): kind of conferences that we can draw a conclusion from at those hotels. That's a good call. Maybe
she
Speaker 236: was able to afford New York as a lady of the night. Well, I wondered. I wondered. I think Eric Kirk was in Mossad or CIA
training
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): when she was hiding those eight months. Or pregnant.
Speaker 272: Married sugar daddy isn't uncommon at all. Oh, you mean she's meeting a married sugar daddy?
Was
Speaker 273: that a thing back then?
Love the opening statement. I
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): live near the Heaven's Gate home where they drank Kool-Aid in their Nikes. What
was up with
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): the Nikes? Did Nike sponsor them or something? Interesting story. If you're not familiar, always wonder how people can live there.
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah. I'm not going to tell you the name of the person. I'm not going to tell you the home he lives in, but
I got a
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): friend and he
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): lives, let's
just say in the
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): Northeast somewhere.
and he was
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): telling me about his house, and he loved his house. He just bought this house not terribly
Speaker 170: long ago. He
was talking
Speaker 170: about how amazing the house was and all this, and he's like, yeah, only catch. And I was like, what? He's
like, kind of
Speaker 170: owned by a notorious person before I moved in. And I said, who? And then he
told me
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): who it was, and I was like, I
don't think I
Speaker 274: would live there. Go
get a
Speaker 274: priest. Wash it down. Apparently,
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): you can buy real estate from really scandalous people. Pennies on the dollar.
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): pennies on the dollar. That's funny, though.
Can we
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): get a close-up on E.K.'s eyebrows as there may lie a clue? I
think she's Ben
Speaker 275: Shapiro in drag? I'd
buy it. Ben kind
Speaker 276: of looks effeminate. She's sort of manly. I
don't think
Speaker 277: she's ever had eyebrows that big, though. He's got, like, school buses parked up
there.
Speaker 277: that's different
oh my gosh does she
Speaker 195: write reviews for companies on TripAdvisor she doesn't have to travel just write a review based on their criteria oh
I don't know I
Speaker 195: don't think so
Speaker 236: though like she's
in
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): some pictures or she took some pictures feels even more likely that EK had a business meeting in some fort on 98 uh-huh
uh-huh gonna be a bit late oh
Speaker 170: getting in a bit
late but
Speaker 170: it's no surprise
to me
Speaker 170: that
And
Speaker 170: cults fizzled out the same time the internet was
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): becoming a mainstream item in society. Well, what would that have to do with it?
We've just
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): transferred our cult like that. Are
you saying
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): we would have all been in a cult?
But now we're
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): just in the chat.
I
Speaker 44: can buy that. Sounds like Erica is a madam.
In my IMO, she wasn't
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): traveling. She was using that as a cover-up. Stock photos only. Honestly, looks sus.
Speaker 278 (lower-pitched voice): Maybe.
notice
Speaker 278 (lower-pitched voice): ritz paris visit said traveled as a couple was this during the cabot phillips days i think so
Speaker 279 (lower-pitched voice): i think that would have been early cabot phillips days but i don't know the earliest i can pin them together is like
june maybe july i
Speaker 280: don't know if
i can get them
Speaker 280: all the way back to
sounds like a transportation
Speaker 281: business to me about a location she visits not too bright to post and critique everything
well did anyone
Speaker 195: accuse her of being part of a
Speaker 206: high iq outfit
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): I'll
Speaker 269: see
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): you next
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): time.
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): Also, she said she was going to get her law degree in 2017 at Liberty University.
Speaker 269: Please investigate that part.
Yeah, but she didn't. She
Speaker 269: got some masters.
Shout out to
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): Daisy. Thank you for being on Team RBP. You're awesome. P.S. Barron, I understand the statement of the empty picture frame.
Keep it blank. Crisis King. Crisis
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): King, indeed. It's going to stay blank.
At least for the
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): time being.
It's
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): going to stay blank.
Boomer upper
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): echelon protocols and trainers and Gen Z smartphone addicts equal digital backlash for three-letter operatives cover up
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): Covert for action?
If it
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): wasn't sad, it'd be funny.
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): So the question, let me rephrase your comment
into a
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): question. The question is, what did they learn during this era of cult study that they're now using on us without our knowledge? And I think the smartphone has a lot of application.
But I also think the infiltration of the churches, they
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): learned a lot
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): there. They learned how far they can push, how hard they can push.
What
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): to do when people start getting second guessing, what
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): political messages they can put in. I mean, I think they learned a lot during this era of Intel operation. So I think
you're, I like your
Speaker 283: comment. Collecting black mail on high ups. Oh,
Speaker 284: yeah, good.
She might have
Speaker 284: seen Brigitte's little Macron.
I don't know. Was EK working for the Travelocity or
Speaker 286: Expedia? She lived...
Speaker 286: More lives than all of us combined. Love your channel,
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): Marion. Thank you.
Yeah, I
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): don't know.
Hoping we
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): get up to five minutes of content before the show ends. What does that mean?
I like how people pay to
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): throw insults. I'll take it.
A little
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): behind, but didn't
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): hear you catch that EK put trip
type as
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): couple. Yeah, I backed up and saw that. Someone sent me a note and said that.
Ritz
Speaker 287: Paris Day. Still you...
I want to
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): know she's not watching, so I'll read it. Still you, above Candace, hit
Speaker 204: the like button. Christ is king. Christ is king, indeed. Do hit the like button. Don't, on nights when
Speaker 87: our principal is not at an event in Washington, D.C.,
don't say stuff like that. I don't want
Speaker 289: to hear CNN. I don't
need to
Speaker 289: make an enemy at it.
Sounds like
Speaker 290: she's working
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): for a travel magazine. I don't
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): know what
Speaker 236: she's doing. According to chat, GBT.
She was
Speaker 236: also the co-founder of Arizona Foothills Charitable Foundation during 2017. Yeah, we've looked into that, pulled the records on that. They didn't do much.
None of
Speaker 236: her stuff did much.
Nice was on the phone
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): with her friend, who is an Orem police dispatcher. Her friend said he had to sign NDA after a big bang,
Speaker 291: and the public knows less than half the truth. Call glitched, dispatcher panicked, and hung up crazy.
Can you secretly email me the
Speaker 292: names?
Speaker 292: Andretti884. Are you related to the Andrettis?
Like Andretti Motorsports? Like
Speaker 293: Mario? Michael? Marco?
That's
Speaker 251: cool. That'd be a cool last name. I
bet if
Speaker 251: you have that last name, you can get caught speeding and be like, it's okay, I'm an Andretti.
Speaker 294: Seriously. I'm safe. We
don't have
Speaker 294: any choice
but
Speaker 295: to drive fast, officer.
Will
Speaker 170: you email me some information about that? I'd love to follow up on that off the record and then
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): see if we can somehow work either some background or on-the-record material out of that. That would be
Speaker 296: amazing.
That would be
Speaker 296: amazing. I'm
going to
Speaker 296: take a picture of this.
See how quick that
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): was?
Speaker 297: I'm getting
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): good at it.
I'm
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): really starting to believe there are a few clones one looks and acts
like a
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): little girl how in the world would we know those her pictures that's
interesting
Speaker 187: about cloning that might be a member show but I am very concerned about human cloning
very
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): concerned I'm very concerned about these closed bases and
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): black sites around the world and entire countries that operate at black sites that aren't really messed with like North
Korea
that
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): have notorious human prisons
Speaker 298: where people are born and die in the same place. I'm very concerned about human cloning.
Erica's whole person is a big
Speaker 299: stick of bull butter. Bull butter comes in sticks?
See, I'm learning
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): from you. Not only does this woman greed differently, but she lives and travels differently as well. Where's the money coming from? Keep up the good work, expose the truth. We're trying, we're trying, we're trying.
Did
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): anyone mention the NYC reviews were all made on the same date? 5-25-2017. Yeah, it looks
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): like what she did was she would log in and do several reviews and then log out and then come back later and log in and do some reviews again.
Hello from Canada. Her
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): review at the
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): Ritz says it traveled as a couple. Maybe she had a sugar daddy.
A lot of people seem to be asking
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): that question.
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): Baron, as a war vet with a very dark sense of humor, you've given me a plethora of jokes about EK with this, and I only wish YouTube would let me say just one. Tried and failed. Darn it.
Keep it
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): clean. It's a family show. Someone should check on web if JE visited any of those spots during the same time as Erica's visits. It really sounds like she was traveling as a paid escort.
Say the quiet part out
Speaker 300: loud.
have you
Speaker 300: checked the big
Speaker 195: global conferences in those places no but we will and particularly security and intel conference see
who in government have
Speaker 49: timelines match or travel u.s and foreign government see this is why we do the shows this is why we do the shows do a show throw some facts out there and the theories come in and now we can run down new theories things i hadn't thought of i hadn't thought
Speaker 301: to do some of
these things
Speaker 301: uh ellsworth
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): air force base is in south dakota
said she was there
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): for a wedding but I
I live in
Speaker 302: Watertown. Why would she be here? Let's look at where Watertown
is. It's kind of
Speaker 170: over by Minnesota. I've
got some
Speaker 170: cousins in Minnesota. They talk like this. I don't know. Is
there nothing
Speaker 170: around Watertown? There's a lot of water.
Speaker 279 (lower-pitched voice): Lake Campesca, Pelican Lake. It kind of looks like
what we
Speaker 279 (lower-pitched voice): had to black out from.
Speaker 303: the david statue really
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): what a weird looking lake
um
Speaker 304: now let's
look up uh air for uh
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): military bases in south dakota see if there's anything near there military bases
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): in south dakota i
do oh there's one right
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): there oh that's just a little rotc thing uh there's
really nothing near
Speaker 184: water i don't know she said she was there for a wedding in
I tend to
Speaker 184: take her to word.
The woman has done
Speaker 305: and seen more things than most of us in eight years than we would do in 40 years.
She's a thing. Maybe the reviews are
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): to distract us from what she was really doing at the time, to appear as a normal person
Speaker 236: doing normal things. It's a fake timeline alibi. God bless you, Baron. Christ is king. Christ is king indeed. That's a great point. I hadn't considered that.
Now I'm
Speaker 236: hungry and want to go
Speaker 195: on vacation, but I'll fly coach.
Price is
Speaker 195: king. Price is king indeed, Jennifer. Yeah,
I don't know
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): why people fly more than coach. You're
going to
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): the same place. Suffer. A couple hours, you'll be fine.
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): I've been to business meetings and hotels when I sold real estate. We actually had classes in banquet rooms. In Paris? In Santiago, Chile?
Erica sounds like a
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): snob.
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): she'll never be happy chasing worldly things true joy comes from family and a relationship with our savior jesus christ she gives me theick as the kids say
Speaker 307: helga shabba labba ding dong
Speaker 4: top fleetwood
mac
Speaker 307: fan here songbird all-time fave that is
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): one of my very favorite songs
came to
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): nix in a dream she woke up at 3 a.m with no way
to
Speaker 195: record it played it over and over on a piano until the producer answered her call at 9 a.m to
open the studio did you know
Speaker 195: the story about how they
Speaker 75: recorded it, KT Bliss?
When
Speaker 75: they recorded Songbird, that was a way overproduced album, but it worked.
They rented out
Speaker 18: a theater. I think it was in Berkeley or somewhere in California. And they rolled the piano out, and they put a single flower on the piano. I'm getting chills telling the story. And it had a single light shining over the piano. And
Christine
Speaker 221: McVie sits
down and
Speaker 221: plays it in one take.
and it was
Speaker 221: just, and
Speaker 128: they just recorded the like ambient sound. Beautiful song.
Speaker 308: Beautiful song. It
Speaker 128: gives me chills every time I listen
Speaker 309 (lower-pitched voice): to it. One of my very favorite. I have
Speaker 278 (lower-pitched voice): the album on, finally. It's
under
Speaker 309 (lower-pitched voice): my, it's in my little vinyl case under my desk. EK
didn't
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): travel to those places. No one has, would ever describe these places like this. I spent years traveling and lived in Florence for two years.
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): This was made up for
now
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): you're just calling her a liar. E.K. Side Hustle, professional hotel reviewer, full-time madam.
Say that out
Speaker 310: loud. May have worked for a high-end escort service. Oh, my gosh. This
is all
Speaker 311: just opinion, Andrew and Blake and Mikey. We don't need you blasting us over the place. No one's calling her
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): that. We're
just guessing
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): of things she might have done.
Did Daisy
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): figure out what wedding she was going to that close to
the
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): bad review hotel?
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): Even Daisy has limits.
Speaker 281: Maybe. Modeling agency that EpiPen and her scouted for.
Speaker 313: Could
be. I think Erica
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): forgot to take her glitter outfit back, black heels when she put on a
little Bo
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): Peep outfit with Sarah
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): Huckabee. Yeah, whoever dressed her that. I mean, you're going to meet the governor. You're wearing blue jeans? Really?
Speaker 277: Really? I mean, I know you're talking
to a
Speaker 277: high school, but it's the
Speaker 204: governor of a
state.
Put on
Speaker 204: some slacks.
Reviews could
Speaker 204: be decodable intel messages. I'm
not going down that
Speaker 314: road again. Nope.
There's an Army
Speaker 314: facility
Speaker 195: in Watertown, South Dakota. Google. Army, Watertown, South Dakota.
The Salvation
Speaker 315: Army? Oh, there's a National Guard Readiness Center.
There's a
Speaker 316: U.S. Marine
Corps
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): recruiting place. She has Marine Corps.
But
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): don't most little towns have stuff like that?
Not like a big base or
Speaker 195: anything. David's Wang made me bust out laughing, causing asthmatic coughing. Scared my dog. I
Speaker 213: apologize more.
I should
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): keep it cleaner. The family operation.
Hey,
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): Baron. Great work. Been a while since last super. Keep moving forward. You and Candace are true Americans. The red hoodie matches Miami of Ohio.
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): Yes, they do. Great basketball team to watch. Go Red Hawks. Crisis King. Peace be with you. Crisis King, indeed.
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): Thank you, Ken. And yeah, I've been following, I
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): follow, I don't follow a ton of people on Twitter, but one person I follow is Michael Wilbon, and he loves Miami of Ohio.
I
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): think he went to Ball State, so he's a big Mac guy.
But thank you. A
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): very generous contribution. Thank you.
And Files, a
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): Ghislaine replacement, often recruited girls in EU. Bet she was meeting
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): moms to make look legit. Girls emailed moms. We're concerned a lot. Really? I need
to look
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): into that.
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): E.K.'s a regular at the Church of St. Mattress. But everybody's got sleep.
Ritz-Paris
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): has no affiliation at all with the Ritz-Carlton Hotel Group.
Makes me
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): wonder if her hotel reviews and stays were real or if she's trying to pose that she was living that lifestyle.
I mean,
Speaker 277: pose for whom?
It's not like she's
Speaker 277: advertising. I
don't know. This is for some
Speaker 250: Candace merch for Daisy. Daisy, you are our secret weapon. She is. And she's a big standus.
I work
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): in LP. People can freelance as talent and claim as modeling. They are considered product specialist experts. People will train
them to
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): talk about the product. Wonder if anyone knows if associated with
agency as
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): a hire. That's
a good thought. Writing
Speaker 195: reviews is a job. Lots of websites for that. She doesn't have to actually go anywhere to do it. Could explain self-employment. Yeah, but she only had like 80 reviews. I mean, how
much you
Speaker 122: making off each one? You're not making thousands of dollars per review.
baron
Speaker 122: got some people looking into at their knuckles after
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): the show i'm over here secretly investigating my wife don't look at your wife's knuckles bro don't do it got
good
Speaker 318: knuckles see those good knuckles yeah
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): people
look people
Speaker 318: look i look at
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): people's knuckles all the time that's how i judge
them i
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): look at their knuckles to see if they're gonna ask for my leftovers
How is
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): she eating all that pasta in Italy but then gluten-free eating a lettuce burger one month later in Chile? Does In-N-Out offer gluten-free options? I don't know the answer to any of those questions. She did say that one of the pasta
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): places had good gluten-free options. I
noticed she
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): wasn't reviewing pizza or sandwiches, salads and whatever. So yeah, it could be gluten-free. I don't know.
Ian is creating
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): a timeline with Einstein locations. Cross-reference EK travels. Love your show.
Good.
Speaker 250: That's a good note.
Speaker 250: Edge, why does she mention clean? Is she in the habit of staying in sketchy hotels? Has she worked a day? She
needs a
Speaker 250: reality jolt. Well, it sounds like she was
working a
Speaker 250: lot. Not sure what she was doing. Not making any allegations,
Speaker 286: Blake, Andrew, Mikey.
Just noting she
Speaker 286: does a lot of business meetings in hotels. I
sent $20
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): last week, but my message did not go through with it. So here it is again. I got rid of Netflix and got YouTube Prime. Game
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): changer. God bless.
I
Speaker 319: like YouTube Prime or premium or whatever it's called. I like it a
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): lot.
Big
Speaker 320 (lower-pitched voice): fan. Brandon Tatum got married in Watertown, South Dakota in July 2017. I'm 15 minutes behind. You might say this.
For
Speaker 321: real? For
real, for
Speaker 321: real?
Does
Speaker 161: anyone know if
Speaker 148: Charlie was at that wedding? Can anyone put Charlie Kirk at that wedding? We're going to pause, and we're going to do a little research here.
Great intel,
Speaker 322: Drew. Thank you.
Was
Speaker 57 (lower-pitched voice): Charlie Kirk at Brandon Tatum's wedding in
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): Watertown, South Dakota?
In
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): July 2017, we'll
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): see what AI has to say about that.
He's searching as
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): we speak, and it's a he. Let's just be honest.
No
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): relevant results. I
know someone I can ask. Someone who works at
Speaker 324: TPUSA who would have access to the calendar.
Yes, yes,
Speaker 324: yes.
Do you
Speaker 114: know if Charlie Kirk was at Brandon Tatum's wedding in July of 2017? We're
going to get to the bottom of
Speaker 127: this,
Speaker 162: ladies and gentlemen. What was she doing at a political wedding in 2017? I guess she could have been with her boyfriend, who at the time was Cabot Phillips. Maybe he was there.
But that puts
Speaker 162: her in this circle.
is the
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): only regimen change that's
needed for peace. Okay. Only tourist
Speaker 169 (lower-pitched voice): attraction in Watertown, South Dakota, Art Center. I
follow our Lord,
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): God, and Savior, Eastern Orthodox Jesus Christ, for he is King of kings and Lord of lords. BB is dead by
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): choice. Did
you guys check to
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): see if the photos, Erica Kirk,
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): erica took were taken from the internet they look professionally taken not a cell phone photo regular camera they don't look like she took them so daisy explained this to me some of those are
her
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): photos some of those are just stock photos from the website from uh whatever the review site she was doing using was
um and
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): and so you have to actually go to her profile to see the ones she
took so some of them are
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): hers and some of them may be photos other people took talk about the mask coming completely
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): off with old bb he said that with his chest and
meant it yeah
I pray
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): everyone hears this and responds accordingly. Christ is king. Christ is king indeed. Thank you.
Yes,
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): battle blood, barren red. Now with Israeli queen E, E.K. outed and al yahoo, dropping truths
with
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): Jesus. No chance against Genghis Khan. 2016, Khan be the year we get
free from
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): the slave spell. I hope people listen to what he
Speaker 203 (lower-pitched voice): said and go, maybe this guy isn't on our team.
It was
Speaker 203 (lower-pitched voice): always a religious war. Please look into that organization that is seeming to get people banned when they talk about it. So I'm not going to
say it
Speaker 203 (lower-pitched voice): out loud, but you
Speaker 325: guys can see what he's saying. Do
you think these reviews
Speaker 326: could be coded messages, transmissions? It's a thought. It's a thought. I'm not sure. The clip of BB insulting Jesus
Speaker 195: needs to be clipped for X. It's all over X. That's where I found out. That's why I didn't credit anybody. It's like 400 places. People can't seem to understand they are not on our
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): side, yet we are fighting their war. That's correct. Correct.
we're
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): fighting their religious war.
They think
Speaker 161: Jesus is in hell burning in doo-doo. And the Virgin Mary is a person who might do business meetings in hotels. They are chosen and can treat everyone
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): else as animals.
Speaker 327: Read
the Talmud. That's the rumor. That is the
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): rumor on
Speaker 142: that.
Check out and see if our
Speaker 142: grumblers have anything to say.
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): uh please pray for the family of jimmy gracie they found his body today and i can't imagine the pain his family's going through
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): his mom is a colleague and we were together at bama homecoming last fall
i wonder what
Speaker 329: happened that sounds young that sounds college age right now they're saying we will do
that uh pray for the
Speaker 250: repose of the soul of jimmy
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): gracie and his family
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): Arizona Foothills Charitable Foundation was with Michael D., the publisher and CEO of Arizona Foothills magazine. D. grew up in Chicago, media that delivers by D. focuses on high-end living and posh resorts.
You would
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): never guess that D. was also in Mexico, the
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): media company in Scottsdale, Arizona, showing permanently closed. Instagram in Mexico and website in Mexico. Say otherwise. I
would never have
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): guessed that. You're right.
uh
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): but baron show some love to your grumblers i am jojo
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): we're grumbling as we speak uh
crispy christy
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): gnome is from watertown south dakota really and so
apparently is
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): brandon tatum's wife former
nyc professional of
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): 15 years running joke was that the only people old business meetings in fancy soho bars were of a particular profession
allegedly
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): go max
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): Psalm 53.1, B.B. We
haven't read
Speaker 65: from the Psalms in a while. Pretty
easy to
Speaker 331: find. It's kind of in the middle, right?
Oh,
Speaker 332: 35. That's
close to my
Speaker 332: favorite
Speaker 333: Psalm, which is 51, by the way.
Speaker 333: psalm
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): 53 1 just says for the leader according to mahala a moscow of david maybe you got the wrong one there
um yeah
Speaker 254: psalm 51 is dope if you've never read it heart-wrenching
Speaker 195: heart-wrenching
uh saying
Speaker 195: netanyahu is anti-christian over
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): simplistic he and the state he represents are not only anti-christian they are anti-human and you better believe them when they say what they say
baron tr clip from the other day
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): doorbell cams usually hit 15 to 30 feet uh 50 max residential streets are 24 to 50
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): feet so how did it catch someone across the street and in a field nasa doorbell pro. I don't know the answer to that. Um,
I
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): think I can set my cameras up to take the street. I just have them
kind of
Speaker 309 (lower-pitched voice): hold down so they just cover the yard. Because otherwise, every time a car goes by, they light up.
Pharaoh found out
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): and isn't here to tell his story. Does he want to try Jesus? The Lord Jesus Christ is who he says he is. All powerful. I agree.
Traveling with
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): mom. AZ Tech International and Tech Metrics International. U.S.,
Speaker 334 (lower-pitched voice): Latin America, Europe. Business locations. You get the CIA director if you're an agent.
Speaker 334 (lower-pitched voice): Love you, GBC. Take care of family.
Christ is king. Christ is
Speaker 334 (lower-pitched voice): king, indeed. That could be her mom.
Could be her mom. Travel reviews
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): seem like diary entries. Giving four stars to a place most of us peasants will never
be able
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): to afford to see is wild. I'm
all four
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): people watching, but I think she's trying to learn how
to be a
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): person. Christ is king.
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, so that's interesting you say that because...
That's one
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): of the things psychopaths do. They watch humans to try to figure out how they're supposed to emote. You're
spot on
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): about Bibi. You said it so beautifully and clearly. I agree with you 100%. Thank you for what you said. Love you, Baron. God bless you, brother. Jesus Christ is king. He and DJT are two peas in a pod. Christ is king indeed.
Speaker 70 (lower-pitched voice): I'm so worried. I was so worried about DJT when he said that he
didn't think he
Speaker 70 (lower-pitched voice): was going to heaven.
But
Speaker 70 (lower-pitched voice): why are we being led by somebody who thinks he's going
Speaker 335: to hell?
That's scary. Scary. Yeah,
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): Ritz traveling as a couple.
Correct. Kushner &
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): Co., J. Sis, is adjacent to Baccarat Hotel.
It's the Baccarat Hotel. Oh, in New York? I believe you. I'm not going to argue with you
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): over locations in New York City.
Speaker 250: Uh, regarding Satan, Yahoo's message, not taking advice from demon crisis, King crisis, King, indeed. I am not taking his advice either.
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): Trump posted himself. Uh, Trump himself posted on one seven, 2025, that T
S BB
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): is
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): deep, dark, son of a gun. Um, I
believe you did the
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): reviews end in summer
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): 2017. They did. They did. They stopped in like July of 2017. She just sort of gave up on
the
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): travel review live please make a shareable clip of your comment on bb's statement god bless you um
okay you're not alone baron and we need to
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): all use our voice i'm not religious but even i can recognize evil when i see it
finally got to catch
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): a live love your show you
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): candace and coach are my go-to podcast you sound well informed and very
entertained uh wait
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): a minute i know you
do you
Speaker 8: think bb ultimately wants to take over other parts of the middle east yes and i'm pretty sure i know
you are
Speaker 225 (higher-pitched voice): you and my family i'm pretty
sure you are tell your husband i
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): said hello he's a gentleman and a
scholar uh trump's
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): mentor was ray cone it's not new yeah yeah
the
Speaker 337 (lower-pitched voice): most satanic thing I ever heard a world leader say was I can shoot somebody on fifth Avenue and they will still love me.
He did say
Speaker 338: that, didn't he?
I
Speaker 339: forgot. He said that
that was during what
Speaker 339: 2016 or is that 2020
Speaker 337 (lower-pitched voice): during one of the other campaigns? Please
look up
Speaker 337 (lower-pitched voice): Rachel Corey for the audience. Why?
Speaker 337 (lower-pitched voice): What'd she do?
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): American nonviolence activist and diarist crushed by an Israeli
Speaker 340: bulldozer? Holy mackerel.
They just ran
Speaker 340: her over?
Wow. That was dark. I don't want to see
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): the video.
I
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): didn't realize TripAdvisor photos are from other people. Her reviews seem like lies. She's a compulsive liar. This is crazy. She's been lying a long time, writing reviews on the couch for fun. So we don't know that. Again, if you go to, and I'm not going to keep saying it because I've said it multiple times, but if you go to her
actual
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): TripAdvisor profile, which is France Faye, you
can see
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): the ones she took versus the ones other people took.
So I
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): don't want to attribute all of them to lies.
When
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): Tyler Robinson had the four minutes to change his clothes and leave
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): his gun, he had to put his gun back together in that four minutes as well, correct? I think
Speaker 278 (lower-pitched voice): they changed their story on that, and they said he did not disassemble his gun after the Big Bang, which
creates a real problem
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): because when he jumps off the roof, there's no gun. Like
there's a
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): towel or something, but there's no gun. I
love your shows, but everyone
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): on the social
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): should post the BB Blasphemy for all to see. I agree.
djt is
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): a trapped in demonic delusion resistant to transparency but god's
Speaker 250: transparency is shining in and through us keep up the obedient journey we see we believe thank you thank you those are kind i mean
that's that's
Speaker 250: exactly what we need they
can have a jewish
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): nation muzzles nation we can have our christian nation p.s my first super
chat uh
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): no that's that's racist you're not allowed to say that
uh for the
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): comments saying the pod is too religious cool find another one then christ is
I
Speaker 342: mean, I'm going to do the show we're going to do. You're Where
in the World is Erika
Speaker 175: Fransfey. I heard Carmen Santiago. You started talking about Santiago, 44
Speaker 195: years old here.
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): I know you know that genre.
Speaker 195: Oh, man. I had the computer game. I had the books. I
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): love that Carmen Sandiak. Amen,
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): Baron. You uplifted my faith and soul tonight. Thank you. You've just uplifted mine.
Your voice is
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): so important. Blessings and prayers to you and your family. Christ is king. Christ is king indeed. Thank you.
Revelation
Speaker 41: 13 describes two beasts. The first beast is the Antichrist, the political leader. And the second beast is the false prophet, a religious leader.
Oh. Oh.
Speaker 344: Okay. Okay.
but
Speaker 345: that didn't also describe anyone who rejects the humanity of Jesus's or the divinity of Jesus is an antichrist also when there's something like that in there
I have to go
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): back and look thank you Baron for saying pick aside that is how I became Catholic one year coming up on Holy Saturday Christ is my Savior yeah
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): that it seemed like I
I'm a
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): convert it seems like I I converted just recently but I did the math the other day it's been 18
Speaker 250: years
that's a
Speaker 346: long time long time time flies when you're having fun
Speaker 250: hey bear my little brother passed 10 months ago publicly i will never
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): watch national news or viral videos thank you for fighting for ck you've given me motivation to get out of bed and
find a
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): solicitor um well jitterbug gm first i'm very sorry for your loss terribly
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): sorry um but i encourage you yeah find somebody to
take justice
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): if that's what you need um
Speaker 347: Helicopters are back Pull that one
Speaker 46: up Is that the pizza
Speaker 348: copter again? If
I have to
Speaker 54: go Oh gosh, it's getting close, guys What's going on? Who is it?
oh
Speaker 349: gosh I
don't
Speaker 350: know if you guys can hear that it's loud that's crazy I
Speaker 295: don't know what I'm saying
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): but I hope I hope you're able to find some peace
Speaker 203 (lower-pitched voice): I genuinely do and we'll certainly pray for you and your family been
Speaker 337 (lower-pitched voice): using DMSO for a nine month runny nose better already
I used
Speaker 192: it for a runny nose, and I think it fixed my vision. I
used to wear
Speaker 192: glasses. See
Speaker 250: forever now. Bibi talks about game, but he can't fight his own fights. We have to stop enabling this monster. Agreed. Einstein
was in
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): Paris at the same time. Go to jmail.world and type in Paris, April 2017. A few of her travel dates coincide with his. No! No!
Is
Speaker 351: this true? Daisy, I need your help. Is
this
Speaker 352: true? Oh,
it's spelled a
Speaker 259 (lower-pitched voice): rule.
Speaker 353: I'm so in the habit of typing Gmail. I'm
Speaker 259 (lower-pitched voice): not able to type it in.
Is it
Speaker 354: really? What did you say? April 2017? Oh, Paris, April 2017.
He
Speaker 355: was. No.
No.
Speaker 357: he was
May
Speaker 358: 10th to 16th Paris May 17th Paris
oh
Speaker 359: Thank you.
That is crazy. No
Speaker 361: way.
Speaker 362: I
am just in awe right now. I'm
Speaker 285: speechless. I'm genuinely speechless right now.
i need to
Speaker 285: rant
Speaker 334 (lower-pitched voice): on a clip i need this rant on a clip to send to my family
Speaker 363: you're free to clip it went and
checked i
Speaker 334 (lower-pitched voice): liked the show before it started and it was gone how rude
Speaker 364: thank you for all you do crisis king uh crisis king yeah everybody go check your likes i guess i didn't know that they went away um fired
up preach brother canadian alt lefty
Speaker 364: who
Speaker 365: hate stems and lips
I
Speaker 365: don't know what an alt-lefty is. I know what a Canadian is.
51st
Speaker 175: stater. I'm just kidding. I'm just messing with you. I'm just messing with you. I
know a
Speaker 175: person that has a similar lifestyle to Erica's. Turned out she was trafficking drugs. Well,
Speaker 195: I
haven't ruled that out either. Will
Speaker 195: Netanyahu's Israel usher in the Antichrist? Well, we may be looking at him.
Hey,
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): Barron, thank you and your team for all the excellent research you do. Do you happen to have a link for
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): the Catholics for Catholics event tonight? You and Candice make me want to move back to Nashville. Are you going to run by at the last second? If
you search
Speaker 366: Catholic for Catholics, Catholic
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): prayer for America, it is tonight at 6 p.m., and it's Eastern time, so you're late.
I
Speaker 257: don't think they're streaming it live I don't believe oh
they are
Speaker 257: streaming it live
Speaker 212 (lower-pitched voice): yeah so just search it Catholics for Catholics
prayer for
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): America if you search that up you'll
find it and it's on
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): YouTube I'll have to watch it later
do you
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): think it's possible EK was paid to do these reviews or got free stays or something and that she was not actually doing business no I don't think so I don't think so
Most
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): don't believe in Kintrails. No hope.
I don't
Speaker 78: know. Hey, Based Daddy Baron. Based Daddy Baron? Wow.
Hope it's
Speaker 78: the cool gin thing is here too. LOL. We're coming back to the
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): Catholic Church in waves. It is rad. Six months ago, I was doing tarot.
Now I'm
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): an OCIA. Crisis King. Crisis King indeed. The tarot stuff scares me to death.
Speaker 139: Tarot, Ouija boards, palm reading, crystal ball looking.
Speaker 139: future that stuff scares me to death
and i'm not even
Speaker 326: saying it's inaccurate i think the demons are telling people what to say scares me excellent opening statement christ can go max christ king indeed thank
you i'm literally in
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): tears right
now to
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): hear that evil man say that about our lord and savior jesus christ with whom i love with my
whole heart yeah it was
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): it made me angry it's why i don the red sweatshirt
i just
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): emailed my pastor at world outreach church near nashville about bb Thank you. Jesus is King.
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): I
Speaker 334 (lower-pitched voice): know where that church is.
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): It's on the
Speaker 334 (lower-pitched voice): corner of Old Hickory
and Granny
Speaker 334 (lower-pitched voice): White, right?
Is that right? It was, I mean, I
Speaker 367: remember it
from when I grew
Speaker 367: up there.
Unless you're talking about
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): one in another city.
Maybe that's not what it was called. Yeah, Bethel World
Speaker 368: Outreach
Speaker 369: Church.
Granny White
Speaker 369: Pike. I don't know if it's the same one.
But it's been there
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): forever.
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): keeping all truth tellers in my prayers thank you for all you do thank you I
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): wish Erica would have been exposed years ago I wonder what her ex-boyfriends are thinking now after seeing everything unfold over the past few months
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): yeah they might have been in on it Project Constitution
got a
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): cease and desist did he really? I
got to look
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): that up
did he post
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): about it?
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): Project Constitution
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): Oh yeah Why is TPSA This is great I'm going to show this
He
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): always
Speaker 371: writes The longest posts Like
Speaker 270: I
Speaker 372: picture him In a dark room somewhere With just like Notes everywhere And just flailing
Speaker 25: about Angrily at the keyboard Jordan.
Speaker 25: exclusive why is tp usa sending me legal cease and desist letters they are back
Speaker 256: to trying to threaten lawfare to silence journalists
they can't
Speaker 256: answer the question so they sent the lawyers i received a formal cease and desist from south bank legal on behalf of erica kirk and tp usa demanding i delete my post and apologize for defamation my response is simple i'm
Speaker 373: not backing down
um oh that's
Speaker 373: about that recording yeah that see i never
Speaker 374: thought that was her
oh they got
Speaker 373: other ones
Speaker 375: Every other post they take issue with.
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): Oh, I see what he's saying. Okay,
Speaker 376: well.
Speaker 149: Yeah. That's interesting. How do you delete it if they tell you to preserve the evidence?
Speaker 377: TPSA is only trying to take Daisy away from you and put her on something other than EK. Oh, are they?
Daisy, don't go. When
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): you shared the song for your daughter, it made me think of my dad. He passed three years ago and I miss him so much. You're only 10 years older
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): than me, but you give off such dad energy and it makes me love your show even more. Thank you for being you. Can
I translate that? You're
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): old.
I
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): mean, that's what I heard. I'm not sure what you meant when you said it, but all I heard is, hey, old
Speaker 116: man, you're old.
And you're doing
Speaker 116: old man stuff. At least you call me dad, not grandpa, like the other guy did.
I'll allow
Speaker 116: it, Lydia.
Thank you
Speaker 116: for the compliment. I appreciate it. I
mean, sometimes
Speaker 277: people are old. It happens.
It beats the alternative. You know, worm
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): food. I'm convinced Bibi and Trump trying to start a religious war and or give cover to a patsy to do a...
red
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): flag attack. You
mean a
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): false flag
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): attack? I
think you
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): might be right. I pray you don't betray us by putting Trump's pick back up. That
would be
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): unforgivable. We are on no pace
Speaker 156: to do that anytime soon.
Husker Red
Speaker 379: Adidas, thank
you for
Speaker 379: representing. You think I'm from Nebraska?
Oh, my daughter was
Speaker 187: sent a card for Mrs. Teen Illinois, but it cost $1,800 to go. My dad put it, paid it,
Speaker 236: but then came everything else. Long story short, the winner spent $15,000 dollars
on
Speaker 236: all the things love you crisis king crisis king indeed love you too hey are you telling me she bought her way to miss arizona usa
but listen the
Speaker 236: exorcist files on spotify per your recommendation it is great such an insight keep up the amazing work man love and prayers from australia
um i
Speaker 236: love the
Speaker 380: exorcist files my whole family loves baron
have
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): you read the instability of truth i have not thanks for all you do thank you for the uh kind contribution by the way i'm catholic forgot to say that in super chat uh duly noted duly noted
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): Richens has the same attorney as Tyler Robinson. That's correct. She did that trial. Have you checked? That video was real. I've not seen any other posts about it. If true, I want to share with my pastor. God bless you for Super Chat. Love your show. I mean, it's going around as if it's real.
I assume it is. Been busy
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): with high school b-ball state championship
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): games. I
need to
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): get caught up on your lives. Sorry.
You are forgiven. Our girls b-ball
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): team won their division and class state championship here in Tennessee.
First one
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): ever. Well, congratulations.
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): congratulations a big accomplishment clip of BN is damning and you'll persuade people he
is evil
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): people under his spell will make excuses for this
Speaker 365: though maybe the antichrist spirit has already a fatal grip on them sobering I'm starting to wonder that because isn't that the thing that the the antichrist comes and he tricks
believers into
Speaker 365: believing
Speaker 377: these evil things that's sort of what's happening
In the
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): black box behind you, you should write who killed Charlie Kirk, how, and why. Once a question is answered, you cross it out. A kid. No, you won't. Yeah, I'm not
going to
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): do that. Satan, Yahoo is dead and in hell. Video is AI. I leave open
the possibility. Anyone see the
Speaker 18: jinx? Life and death of Robert Durst. He
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): left the paper trail. So did money-loving Erica who cursed herself. Matthew 6, 24. I have not seen that, no. Is it good?
Sounds
Speaker 250: good.
Speaker 250: Everyone, if you can, please talk about food, water,
Speaker 381: and buy seeds.
Love and
Speaker 381: peace to you all. Christ is king. I don't think you're talking about bird seeds. I'm
a little scared. There are seeds in my
Speaker 25: medjool dates. Does that count? I
kind of
Speaker 25: bought seeds
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): when I bought the medjool dates. Oh,
man, that
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): makes me want one.
those
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): reviews during her travels appear to me to be a cover for intelligence work
Speaker 250: and or
communication back to
Speaker 250: her handlers. Nobody was reading her reviews,
by the
Speaker 250: way, Erica and intelligence work would be ironic. I
Speaker 116: agree. I agree. I remember an interview with Charlie and he said how many days a year he was on the
road and
Speaker 116: not home. I think it was like 280. I'm
sure if he
Speaker 116: spent more time with EK, he would have figured her
Speaker 169 (lower-pitched voice): out. Yeah, I've wondered that. Especially when she talks about all the times he was,
you
Speaker 320 (lower-pitched voice): know, daddy's home, Shabbat Shalom. How
many times was
Speaker 170: he really there on Friday?
i thought
Speaker 170: ek spent all of 2017 locked in a room
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): praying no that was 2008 2008 um welcome
Speaker 66: to the club brother you read way too many of those reviews i don't even know
how it
Speaker 66: ended because i just skipped you reading the supers
and whatever they were good you should have
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): watched you learned a lot about her life all right regency in santiago chile was the host of the World Copper Conference in April 2017.
I don't
Speaker 382: think she's in the copper business.
You know who
Speaker 383: is in the copper business? I'm
just
Speaker 384: saying. I'm
not just
Speaker 385: saying. I mean, he is, but I'm not saying. I'm not suggesting anything. I was joking.
Hi,
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): Baron. EK recruiting models in hotels. Check out Jay Bullions and sister. He's been very active in South Africa. Christus vinked
it.
Speaker 195: You see, my Latin sucks. Belated happy patties.
Speaker 116: Now you're switching to Irish.
You hit me with
Speaker 116: all that Latin and go straight to Irish.
Happy patties
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): to you, sir.
When the
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): word says, every knee will bow, every tongue will confess that Jesus
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): is Lord, it means every. Those who do not will find themselves
in the
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): goat lane when he says, you're who? Jesus compels
us to love thy
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): neighbor, but these are demons manifesting.
My
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): honest assessment, are
Speaker 170: we supposed to love them too?
You can
Speaker 170: love them, but you don't have to follow them into wars.
You know what I mean? You
Speaker 148: don't have to, like, worship them at church on Sunday.
Screaming amen after
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): every pause when you were preaching against that vile antichrist because Christ is king and the
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): almighty, period. Christ is king indeed. I agree with you. Question. Have I, uh,
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): I have been brought up in the Christian church. I've been pulled towards Catholicism this past year. How would I go about converting or learning more info? Call your local parish. They'll have an OCIA program. It's late. It's Easter. But they can talk
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): to you about getting started next year. But that's how. Just talk to your local folks, and they'll
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): explain the whole process to you.
And you can read
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): Rome Sweet Home by Scott Hahn in the meantime.
I
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): will say we Catholics also consider ourselves Christian. It's
possible that her
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): meetings were an embellishment and that she was just attending various conferences
related to
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): mommy's business, business experience for mom, and EK gets a fun gap year. Yeah,
Speaker 3: maybe. I raised that possibility as well. I'm deeply disturbed by what
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): Bibi said. It seems deliberate like DT played into his trap. DT is on bended knee
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): to Bibi as he spits in the face of Christian nation that's been their biggest ally.
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): That's an interpretation that may not be wrong.
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): E.K. was an... I don't know that we can say that. Pretty Woman, Einstein Ties. I mean, we've all fought it, but I don't know if we can say it. Christ, Charlie Kirk thought he could save her, but later realized he was being set up.
It may not
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): have known.
Guy in
Speaker 386: tan, Rick Cutler detonated the mic to blow. I don't
know about
Speaker 388: that.
maybe
Speaker 389: better than the palm gun theory high end call girl I sick Charlie didn't deserve any
of what he went
Speaker 389: through Jesus loves you
again I
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): mean this is just opinion we don't know this and I'm not certainly want to be on the record calling her that I've
thought
Speaker 390: it
Speaker 314: I've wondered great timing talk about Trump's Christian remarks 10
Speaker 150: minutes after Trump bragged about F-35 flying freely over Iran it was bomb Thank
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): you.
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): Oh, gosh, was it really? Praying for our troops. Did we lose an F-35 over Iran?
Speaker 259 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, makes emergency landing.
Oh, pilot
Speaker 391: stable. Good.
We don't want
Speaker 392: anyone in harm's way.
Speaker 342: former Jehovah's Witness here. All mind control and it's cult. I'm currently shunned only because I don't want
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): to be one anymore. See, I've never looked into him much. I don't know much about him. Sorry
you had
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): that experience. Baron, with all the good info, you and Daisy Fine, how do you pick, choose,
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): what info to pass on to Candice? I mean, we kind of have an open line of communication where we talk about ideas, but she does her show and I do mine. So...
I
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): don't pass information on for her to cover. Sometimes I will give her a heads up of what I plan to cover in the next week or two, just to kind of, you know, make
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): sure we're
not both
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): inventing the wheel at the same time. Maybe, uh, we had a conversation like that last couple of days. So I, um, you know, cause if she's working on, if she's like, Hey, I'm working on the same thing. I'm doing that show tomorrow. Well, I'm not going to waste the whole day working on it,
you know?
So it's
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): not really passing
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): things on to her. I'd
like to know why
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): E.K. is so interested in the Luigi
Speaker 393 (lower-pitched voice): Mancione case. Is it a circumstantial case? Does she know something we don't? I didn't know she was interested in it.
That's news
Speaker 393 (lower-pitched voice): to me.
1 John
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): 2.22, who is the liar if not the one who denies that Jesus is the Christ? This is the one is the Antichrist, the one who denies the Father and the Son. That's
what
Speaker 250: the verse is. Thank
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): you, thank you,
thank you.
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): Barron, has anyone checked these sugar daddy sites for Erica? I mean, if she clearly didn't have a job but was getting money, this could be. Lots of pageant girls are on it, but under
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): aliases. I doubt
she's still on
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): it, though, right? I mean,
I don't
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): think she was probably
Speaker 170: ever on one, but if she was, that was eight years ago. Do they, like, keep an archive, a searchable
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): archive? That seems dangerous. Thank you,
Jesus, for
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): Mr. Barron. Well, thank
Speaker 394: you, Jesus, for Ms. Sarah Bryan being part of the program. Thank you.
What
Speaker 394: broke Barron a minute ago?
Did Barron
Speaker 395: break? Oh,
that was an hour ago. Did I
Speaker 396: just clock that E was on the Egyptian plane? I
don't know about that. The polygamous
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): LDS family fled to Mexico in the 1800s. They include Mitt Romney's family. Read Book Mormons
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): in Mexico by F. Lamontullus. I'll just take your word for it. I don't have time to read that.
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): TripAdvisor could be an Intel tool. Post contained code words just so you get on it.
Yeah, that
Speaker 195: scares me.
It's a
Speaker 195: good day when I can do my kids' event in between your podcast. Oh.
Glad I could help you out. Mary, do
Speaker 195: you think TPSA and Scientology have merged? Big donors are very cult-like, just saying? I don't think so.
Where's that guy's
Speaker 365: wife, by the way? Does she ever show up?
Where is
Speaker 365: Will Smith to smack BB's face and tell him to keep Jesus' name out of his freaking mouth?
Speaker 263: Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Speaker 263: keep my name out your mouth
my wife's
Speaker 263: name out your mouth jt massey
Speaker 397: equals erica lane massey maybe elm no
i mean i think it
Speaker 397: was erica lane management daisy you got a
fan got a fan trump and melania
Speaker 397: visited vatican city in 2017 who
did
Speaker 393 (lower-pitched voice): they at the same time
well she didn't though
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): she just took a picture from the outside
Great
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): show, Baron. Interesting fact. BB went to my high school, Chesterton High School.
Speaker 250: Excuse me, Cheltenham High School. Wincoat PA. Graduated 64.
Duly
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): noted. Duly noted. For me, it was EK talking about TPSA at her wedding reception speech and TPSA sponsoring the reception. And they had it on the ninth
Speaker 152: anniversary of TPSA and also a fundraiser.
She sold merch at her
Speaker 3: husband's funeral.
And then got on the
Speaker 3: radio, got on a call a few days later and bragged
Speaker 398: about it.
Speaker 398: So let's not be too shocked.
Have you seen
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): Veryllium's new video, Goyvid and Ben DeNoon's video on BB being in a coma? He's sort of like an older you. Finally, someone older than
me made me
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): edit, won't send. I have not seen that, but thank you for the heads up. Have you ever thought about looking into the Anne Heche controversy? Supposedly her dead and burned, but sat
up on a gurney, no
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): burns.
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, I did. I've looked into it. I've not thought about doing a show on it. Yeah, that's a wild story.
The
Speaker 250: BB Vermin crawled out of his cave to mock Jesus. It's so insane to me how Christians can still support this. Feeling very frustrated lately. Thank you for going, Max, Barron, and Daisy. Your intelligence is refreshing. Well,
Speaker 66: thank you. Kind words. From the Grumblers, Ohioan here. When Indiana beat OSU in the championship game, I said, I'll allow it because I'm a Barron fan.
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): Good, good. We're finally working you guys over to the good side.
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, from Dom Hollywood and tech bros are ops Erpenbeck in CA and
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): COVID tried Hollywood. Rubio was the deep state guy in 16. Cabot was the digital grassroots director for Rubio's bid and also worked for campus reform.
How did she meet Cabot
Speaker 250: Phillips? If she wasn't in politics,
they didn't live in
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): the same city.
How did she meet
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): him to start dating him?
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): Ellen loved pizza, right? April 14th, 2016, Cabot Phillips and family on Ellen's show. Then 2019,
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): we see Cabot Phillips post on Instagram with pizza lip tattoo. Urban Beck and Colvette were in Hollywood.
And Dom, you
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): squeeze so much into each
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): post. January 2017, Cabot Phillips post on Instagram showing him at TPUSA event, the same Cabot Phillips, January 12th, 2017 post. Erica's comment, there he is.
Speaker 401: Oh, that was in January of 2017?
Hmm.
Speaker 402: Interesting.
Speaker 403: OMG. Just Googled ELK. She
had
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): a few jobs. Attorney, banking, real estate, and military facility management and tech support. I'd be very
cautious of that
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): source. If it's
AI, I
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): would discount it entirely.
uh
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): djt was in rome may 2017 maybe ek maybe he gave ek
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): orders on that trip
she was there in
Speaker 404: march fyi
today is thursday did i say
Speaker 404: it was a different day it's thursday guys palm
Speaker 236: down
first super chat is there a
Speaker 236: possibility to do a long video with all the key points you've uncovered i've re-watched several episodes as refreshers but i love video that brings it all Together, Christ is King.
You
Speaker 84: know how long that show would be?
That would be a long one. Please
Speaker 204: read my email explaining agency's go-sees.
Man, she's working with
Speaker 204: these hotels, staying free and making recommendations, maybe. I
mean, who
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): else makes these kind of posts at every place they stay? Crisis King. Yeah, I don't know. Crisis King, indeed. Are they going to give somebody
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): a free hotel stay for
Speaker 170: making a single review? I mean, that doesn't make sense.
I didn't
Speaker 170: get to catch the entire live. Sorry if I missed this,
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): but was EK following boyfriends around maybe? Staying in those hotels with a boyfriend of the YR? Yeah, maybe. Sounds like that might be why she was in South Dakota for Brandon Tatum's, potentially for Brandon Tatum's wedding, at least
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): at the same time. Hotel Plaza Paris, art exhibition by New York artist Alec Monopoly, April 2017. Well, I doubt that's why
Speaker 305: she was there,
but maybe, maybe.
Speaker 305: listen to the E.K. interview again through the lens. E.K. knew E.K.,
Speaker 236: A.K. knew E.K. and T.B. were handlers that the marriage was a sham, A.K. dropping hints because we're getting close. I'll
listen to it
Speaker 256: again, but I'm
kind of
Speaker 256: replaying portions of it in my head and I
Speaker 405: don't remember him saying anything like that.
I have to watch it. I'll watch
Speaker 406: it again.
Maybe
Speaker 406: Erica worked for
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): TripAdvisor. I don't think so. Maybe. Why wouldn't you just put that on her resume? George, I was the one that designated Whitney Murphy 1989 as
principal two
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): months ago. It's official. No take back.
But
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): that's just the principal. This is the principal. E.K. said she was very interested on how
the trial
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): for Luigi E. Mangione
Speaker 407: would turn out. That's interesting considering it's circumstantial evidence trial. Your thoughts? Yes.
That
Speaker 170: wasn't too circumstantial. He was found
with a
Speaker 408: murder weapon and a
Speaker 75: confession note and a manifesto and the clothes he was wearing and
a bag,
Speaker 75: the same bag. I don't know how circumstantial, I mean, that's not super circumstantial.
BB and
Speaker 305: Huckabee are the Antichrist and mini-Antichrist. Jesus is king. He's like a mini-me. Maybe
someone like Jeff
Speaker 305: Epstein
Speaker 44: was paying for it. Yeah, maybe. I'm
going to
Speaker 44: look through the emails. That April
Speaker 314: connection is so bizarre to me.
Like I'm
Speaker 314: having trouble getting past that.
Maybe her nonprofits pay
Speaker 314: for trips. They don't
Speaker 210: make any money. They can't pay
Speaker 409: that. They don't.
Can you
Speaker 307: support DJT without supporting BB? Also, DJT also keeps saying there's things he can't say. I agree
Speaker 410: with what you say. Maybe CO can get you a meeting.
She cannot get me
Speaker 410: a meeting with Trump.
Two things
Speaker 410: can be true at the same time. BB evil. DJT is God's tool to protect us. He
Speaker 411: said he's not going to heaven.
and
Speaker 412: he's and he launched
Speaker 86: a war targeting civilian infrastructure and killing civilians at the behest of the guy you just said might be evil so no i don't think you can hold those that's that's that's too much cognitive
Speaker 413: dissonance for
me to accept uh where do i
Speaker 413: find the address to send
Speaker 414: something to you and your team i have
a
Speaker 413: p.o box i
don't get
Speaker 236: over there often
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): it's a little
far away
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): but you can send it there, P.O. Box 1258, Spring Hill. I get over there, I try to get over there once a week.
So
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): I'll do my best. I'll do my best. But
that's it if
Speaker 415: you want to look at it.
Super Bowl
Speaker 200: and big sport events
are prime
Speaker 200: trafficking locations. I've heard that, but I don't know the relevance to it.
Speaker 200: Christ is king. Kings and creator of all, period. So grateful for this community. Prayers for all. Prayers for
Speaker 226 (lower-pitched voice): you as well. Christ is king indeed.
She was a
Speaker 226 (lower-pitched voice): bridesmaid in her friend J.C.'s wedding, June 1, 2017, in South Dakota.
But that's not July. That's not
Speaker 417: July.
I'll
Speaker 418: look into that. Thank you. David Bowie was first celebrity close clone MSM interview.
Speaker 417: First celebrity clone MSM interview. I don't know what that means.
Speaker 419: You
got
Speaker 195: me. Hope you get my point of view. Hard to say in 200 characters. Oh.
I don't
Speaker 420: know what you said oh
Speaker 195: oh no I got your message you were the one that was talking about supporting Trump but not BB I mean I got it it's hard for me to swallow Songbird
arguably
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): one of the best songs ever yeah I have a problem with it though she uses just I mean she
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): does it to keep the meter and
all that
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): and the song scans but she uses incorrect English at one point and it always does this to me
when
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): she says i wish it for myself that's not right i wish it for me
um but other than that
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): it's
Speaker 421: perfect but it
Speaker 195: wouldn't scan if she said me it wouldn't sound right the girl gets around bless this high iq outfit oh thank you edit
july
Speaker 3: 1st duly noted oh
you're talking
Speaker 3: about the wedding
Speaker 3: Baron, I wonder if there's a review for possibly, allegedly, maybe a La Quinta
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): hotel meeting near some fort in Arizona or anything near there for that matter. I think she stopped doing the reviews years before that. TripAdvisor, maybe a way to communicate with others in code, romantic people watching.
That's interesting. You
Speaker 251: guys may be onto something. P.S. Athene has
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): five plus pages of search results in Einstein files. I'm down a rabbit hole now and have 12 hour shift in eight hours. Oops.
get
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): some
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): sleep. We'll be here when you get back. Go to bed. Cross-reference these locations, dates with the Egyptian planes or Gulfstream. Again, I can't look back at plane results from eight years ago. It just doesn't work that way. Also, did she ever stop leaving reviews or still doing it? She did stop. She only did it for like a five-month period, four-month period. It was very strange. I
wanted to make you all
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): laugh, so I changed my pick to my cat, Charlie. He
sits like a bloke. A
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): bloke?
I
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): still don't think he's forgiven me for having him snipped. I can't see him. He's too small for me, but I hope everyone else is enjoying the snipped bloke.
I love
Speaker 185: how other
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): people talk. I know ELM ties to Kukorn.
Set PM on
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): Blue
Speaker 250: F. What's Blue F? Guys, there's only one way to reach the show.
Only one way
Speaker 250: to reach the show, and
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): it's in the description on YouTube.
So if
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): you ever don't know the email address, it's in the description on YouTube. Click the description page, slide down. You'll have to click one button to show the email address. I don't know what blue F is, though.
So a PM,
Speaker 208: I'm never going to see. I don't check
PMs
Speaker 422: anywhere else. I'd
say she became
Speaker 422: an agent that year.
maybe
Speaker 423: someone just proved the last bb vid is ai uh you know people keep saying they prove it but i don't know that's the thing i don't know
uh your
Speaker 424: laugh is like popeye
look more
Speaker 129: into rosa i'm surprised
you haven't i
Speaker 129: haven't um
my laugh
Speaker 129: is like popeye
you're the second
Speaker 129: person that said this
i'll pull it
Speaker 425: up
I'm going to
Speaker 425: listen to it in my ear
I don't hear it
Speaker 425: yet You
think I sound like
Speaker 426: that? I'm
only
Speaker 428: slightly offended Only slightly offended It's not bad
That's about it.
uh my
Speaker 429: husband says those pictures erica posted on the review page don't look like the ones she would have taken he said they look like
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): their stock yeah i explained that um go to her page if you want to see the one she took watertown could be watertown new york uh no uh huge army base there tied to fort wachuka 110th mountain division intelligence i know i think it was south dakota
the comment you made
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): about what we're going to do about co the next
Speaker 226 (lower-pitched voice): part of the sentence was i'm not going to dissect
Speaker 430: that autopsy
What are
Speaker 431: we going to do about Candace? Next
part of the
Speaker 431: sentence, I'm not going to dissect that autopsy. I don't
know what you're
Speaker 431: talking about.
ELM
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): extra lunch money ties to CP,
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): PM to Face B. Don't
send a
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): PM to Facebook. It will not be read. I've never read a PM on Facebook ever. So
if you want
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): to email the program, email realbaronpodcast.gmail.com. That's the only way you'll reach me.
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): I don't even look at Facebook that much. And when I do, there's like, I'm not kidding, thousands of Facebook messages. I'm
Speaker 18: not going through them.
So the email is
Speaker 18: monitored. It's up to date. Anything important gets through. But Facebook, don't PM
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): Facebook.
I mean, you
Speaker 226 (lower-pitched voice): can. I'm not telling you you can't, but it's not going to. If you want me to see something, don't do that.
If you just want to get
Speaker 226 (lower-pitched voice): something off your chest, you can, I guess.
Ask
Speaker 236: Daisy to Google what hotel conferences were in Santiago, Chile in April 2017. There was a child internet type conference. Daisy, due for each city. Was there really?
What hotel conferences were in
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): Santiago, Chile in 2017? April 2017.
Was there
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): really?
I
Speaker 355: see the World Copper Conference I'll
leave
Speaker 107: it pulled up I'll look at
it that's
Speaker 107: interesting you should read Colts, Conspiracies,
Speaker 3: and Secret Societies I
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): appreciate all your book recommendations I genuinely do I don't have time to sit around reading a bunch of books I know the books I want to read and I read them I just don't want you guys spending money telling me to read books that I'm never going to read
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): Um, not that they're not good. Um, but I, I like, I have a list of books I'm going to
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): read. I have a way I find books I want to read. And, and I just don't want you guys paying
to tell me to
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): read books.
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): I can't, I can't promise you I'll read.
Um, but
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): thank you for that. I genuinely appreciate it. And maybe somebody else benefits from that. So here, if somebody else wants to read it, cults, conspiracies, and secret societies by Ulther Goldwag.
is a
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): recommended book read. So maybe I shouldn't say that because maybe you're telling other people to read the book. Sorry, I didn't come through right. The only regimen change needed for world peace would be
Speaker 343: that place we can't mention. Oh, I see.
DJ T is the leader
Speaker 343: of the free world because BB is the leader of the enslaved one.
We're the enslaved
Speaker 343: one,
Speaker 65: aren't we?
Speaker 432: Isn't he kind of calling the shots? Isn't that what Marco told us? We didn't
have a
Speaker 432: choice. We had to go to war.
Speaker 433: because BB was going to do it anyway, and it was going to cause his headaches? It sounds like we're the enslaved ones.
The slave doesn't
Speaker 433: call the shots. I'm a sheep. Oh. I'm
Speaker 4: sorry, Big Fat Bird. I've never said those words in that order. I can assure you, and I don't mean anything by it.
Someone in
Speaker 4: the chat said CK
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): was at BT's wedding. BT said it in his rant about EK. Oh,
was he
Speaker 365: really?
which
Speaker 365: means they would have been in the same spot. Probably.
Unless she was
Speaker 200: there for her friend's wedding, JC, whoever that is. We'll
run it
Speaker 200: down. We'll run it down. This won't be hard to find. If
she's
Speaker 393 (lower-pitched voice): talking in code, it would explain why her, she made her reviews on the same day. Maybe conversation with someone. She never at the location.
yeah
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): but again i think some of her pictures are actually from there i don't want to over over read into the uh she wasn't there ritz gate ritz
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): traveled as a couple that's correct uh
ai saying sd
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): wedding was for a brandon pollard i don't listen to ai i'm sorry
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): if you got an actual source i'll listen
to it maybe she
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): never went to any of those places and those are coded messages to other cia agents yeah it could be but again i want to
I don't want
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): to get too far away from the fact
Speaker 3: that she actually took pictures from some of the places there. It's on her account.
Speaker 429: AK
reminds me of
Speaker 434: Meghan Markle leading up to the meeting. Prince Harry, yacht girl, private clubs,
Speaker 18: traveling globally. Where did the money come from?
That's a good
Speaker 18: question. That's what we're all
wanting to
Speaker 18: know. I mean, I'm waiting for you to tell me. Compare
travel
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): with sporting events. Super Bowl equal major traffic. Also, Erica got close and scanned face of grieving mom at State of Union. Most look away when
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): moms cry.
Yeah, but
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): I don't know if you're the second or third person that's made the Super Bowl point,
Speaker 320 (lower-pitched voice): and I'm not getting it if there's a point there. I'm not following it. I mean, I understand what you're saying about the major trafficking events, but I don't understand how it plays into
the
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): story we're talking about today. Any true Christian in the administration would not be able to tolerate what that vile creature said about the one and only Lord of all if they don't stand up for him. They are fake. Someone
needs to
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): address
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): it.
djt has since
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): come to jesus he's saved god bless you christ is king christ is king did he
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): did it the last couple weeks because he said he wasn't going to heaven like two weeks ago three weeks ago
i hope so i
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): hope you're right and
i hope if
Speaker 187: he did then he
can address
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): what the beepster said allegedly said what
i don't know if she
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): were i don't think she
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): worked for him
uh i
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): know elm used different name ties to cp sent yeah
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): i
I
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): don't know if you're the same person, but email. Email that information. RealBaronPodcast at gmail.com.
First,
Speaker 47: Super Chat. I converted to
Speaker 49: Orthodoxy 18 years ago. Congratulations to you, ma'am, Cheryl. That's a long time.
It's a long
Speaker 47: time. I know that because I converted 18 years ago.
Orthodoxy has always
Speaker 47: fascinated me, by the
way. Always
Speaker 47: fascinated me.
Speaker 271: But I, yeah, you
got to pick one
Speaker 149: and go with it, right?
Speaker 149: Please look up EFTA
Speaker 165 (lower-pitched voice): 0, 0, 2, 0, 9, 5, 6, 0, 8. Immediately, please replace O with 0.
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): Okay. I don't know what all that means, but I'll look it up. EFTA dash 0, 2, 0, 9, 5,
6, 0, 8. Let's see
Speaker 435: what, oh, oh, we got a file. We
got a file. Okay.
Speaker 435: what
Speaker 436: does it say government document I don't know what it is
there's no
Speaker 437: text it's
a lot
Speaker 437: easier if you just tell me what I'm going to see Zorn
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): Development Corporation tell me
what I'm supposed
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): to be looking
for
I don't know
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): what that means.
Are we
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): sure the M in ELM doesn't stand for Massey? No, no. But we are sure the website is spelled Erica Lane Management. That's all. I can't rule anything. I can't rule everything out. I can
only apply
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): Occam's razor and say that the day she opened ELM.group, right
before she filed
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): the ELM group
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): paperwork, she also
opened a
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): website called Erica Lane Management. So I just make the connection and assume it's the same.
You'll be
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): wrong. My daughter's getting married Saturday. Please
Speaker 250: pray for Kayla and Chadwick. Will do. They
recently returned
Speaker 250: to church as a couple, and I'm so
proud of
Speaker 250: them. You should be. Danny, you should be.
You should be very proud of them. And congratulations to them. There's also an email
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): from Nick's rabbis, Nick Ravis to JE, asking who they're going to target next. JE says that Charlie was 2017.
I've
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): not seen that even.
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): I figured that would have made the rounds. Will you email that to me? RealBaronPodcast at gmail.com. Erica's connection to Ye is through Calvary Church. Was
Ye part of
Speaker 334 (lower-pitched voice): Calvary Church? Calvary Chapel?
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): Tanya. Calvary Chapel.
That's
Speaker 440: 2019. Well, that would have been too
late, I think. I'll have to look into that. Actually, Calvary
Speaker 443: Chapel does
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): have a Kanye West tag. Oh, is somebody asking if the church should embrace Kanye West? I'll look into that. That's interesting.
One of the
Speaker 444 (lower-pitched voice): most moving shows. I believe this is a test for God's people. God will have the last word. BB doesn't know our God's power. Apparently not. I
fear they
Speaker 444 (lower-pitched voice): ate CK.
Speaker 59: What? You
fear they
Speaker 59: what? I
don't
Speaker 213: know. You must have had a typo there.
she
Speaker 92: was obviously selling the cat oh well that's your opinion not an actual
Speaker 446: i
got it now you
Speaker 184: know where she was working allegedly maybe perhaps yeah well we don't we don't know
i do
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): believe you have surpassed substitute teacher by guy give yourself in daisy credit yeah yeah we we
are we are up
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): to assistant
teacher uh baron
Speaker 195: colmani uh read in And I said, But Ron, come on.
I
Speaker 195: wish I could be of service to the investigation here in Chile. I doubt those
Speaker 170: hotels will give me any information. I'll
do my
Speaker 170: best to ask around. You go, Max.
See something, say
Speaker 170: something, Nat.
Speaker 170: something. I hope my Spanish was up to par
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): for you.
Not only are
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): we high IQ, but you're making honor students of us, and Erica's a real habitual liar. I think she is a demonstrably proven liar
to
Speaker 305: this point yet.
joined
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): early had to take a call now catching up
Florence in
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): 2017 also shows up for Einstein and the J-Men
Speaker 447: no no no
Speaker 448: it
Speaker 356: does
Speaker 449: in April. On
Candace's
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): show yesterday, she showed a photo of Erica in the Mediterranean and wanted to know where she was. Not sure if it's helpful for you, but I figured
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): it out.
She
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): was in Marinkovac, Croatia. Actually, that's interesting because I knew she had spent time
in Croatia
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): before she deleted and privatized everything because of her Instagram stories. So that's interesting that you've identified that.
Was J.E. and
Speaker 281: E.K. meeting candidates in the same city? I'm starting to wonder, guys. This is creepy.
erica's
Speaker 281: ex-boyfriends are probably thinking they dodged
a
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): boule bad joke i know i'll be praying for forgiveness christ is king christ is king indeed i didn't even put that together until you said you'll
pray for forgiveness um
Speaker 3: christ is king indeed running around the house liking you on all my different devices your voice is a necessary and
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): honest one christ is king christ is king indeed i appreciate that commitment to
uh the
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): program i do i do
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): indeed
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): love opening statements and Jesus is the light in life well thank you and you're correct EK tell us you're speaking in code without saying it who else was in these places for meetings more code than my friends and I
Speaker 450: to procure Boone's Farm in high school the strawberry Boone's Farm
we
Speaker 452: knew each other we knew each other I'll be honest with you that's funny
That's
Speaker 452: funny. Hi,
Speaker 236: Baron and Daisy. A stretch, but no stone unturned. Foreign travel meetings as a former Miss Arizona news, newspaper articles over visits. Yeah, maybe we could look
Speaker 122: it up. Thank you for that. Been a Christian for a long time. Over the past year, I've had to pull a pull to Catholicism, went to mass for the first X Thursday
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): to encouragement from you and Candace. Go Max. I
hope you
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): enjoyed it. I hope you enjoyed it.
Speaker 184: Again,
we consider ourselves
Speaker 184: Christian too. I mean, you know, it's not like you're leaving the faith.
Speaker 184: just
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): doing a different version of it. Baron, you calling
out Daisy
Speaker 64: as if she'd burst through the door. I mean, LOL, let's get my pets. Would be great merch. She's so helpful, right? I mean, helpful,
Speaker 195: helpful.
Baron, are
Speaker 195: you interested in title history for Zach Kress? Sure. RealBaronPodcast, gmail.com. Happy to take a look at it.
I disagree
Speaker 195: with you. Ben Shapiro's
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): caterpillars can
jump off
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): the screen and tickle me until I throw up. I hope not. That sounds terrifying.
I don't
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): like getting tickled. Erica's connection to yay is through Calvary Church. Charlie's necklace is the weapon.
Speaker 195: 2025 TN plant that went boom. Look into it. I've looked into it. I've
looked into
Speaker 195: the necklace and the plant. I don't, I hate to toot my own horn. I broke the plant story two days after the plant blew up. I don't, I don't know that anyone broke that had that story before I did. So I've looked into it. Go back and watch that show.
I
Speaker 195: hedged a lot that night. I was like, guys,
Speaker 170: don't know. It might not have anything to do with it.
Maybe Trump
Speaker 170: thinking he's not going to heaven makes him feel freedom to make insane choices. He's
certainly
Speaker 331: doing that.
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): P.S. Psalm 53.1 after intro says, the foolish one says in his heart there is no God. Oh, I could
have kept
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): reading.
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): Barron, what do you think of the Kent Tucker interview? It was disheartened
by the
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): confirmation of how our government
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): is run with war and investigations. Thanks for all you do. I thought it was a good interview. I thought Joe Kent did a good job. He came off very credible, very honest.
What he said about
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): the Charlie Kirk thing devastated
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): me because it
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): sounds like he thought there were leads to foreign actors and
were shut
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): down. And that is unacceptable to me.
That is
Speaker 422: unacceptable. You should not leave it to Candace and Barron and, you know, Ian in the podcasting world to try to figure this out.
Can we just abolish the National Security
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): Act 1947 and conduct the CONUS Truth or Dare Games by Congressional District to do a frame-up restoration of our government? DJT goes first. I
don't think we
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): should be
Speaker 454: recommending anybody be harmed. I don't think that's a smart way to proceed.
now
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): that people have dug into ek i find it odd that gg called charlie by his name rather than
calling
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): him dad seems like top behavior or i'm overthinking
yeah that
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): was weird when she was like charlie cook charlie cook
but you know she's
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): three let's give her a pass but not yet to clown on the
kid um where's
Speaker 455: ek's father you think he'd be defending
his baby girl
Speaker 452: uh he's in arizona
holding
Speaker 170: meetings at hotels are not that unusual when the owners of the company my husband works for in town they often hold meetings at the conference room of the hotel they're staying at yeah
it's
Speaker 311: unusual when you don't have a job that's unusual it's unusual when you
Speaker 66: live in the city you should hold it in your office how are you making money I
think it's a
Speaker 66: little unusual
We're
Speaker 66: losing everything over Iran. I'm just as PO'd as you, man. Yeah, we are. Our country is at grave risk.
Speaker 195: People don't realize it right
Speaker 456: now.
Baron
Speaker 195: TripAdvisor did not offer paid jobs to travel and
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): review hotels in 2017.
Oh, the dog is angry, friends. Angry.
does
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): laurie f also post where she travels hmm it's
a good
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): question i don't know the true antichrist will deceive the whole world even the elect almost he will bring peace
for
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): three and a half years and sudden destruction bb's
close might be
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): the beast um
he's not
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): deceiving me isn't
that coconut
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): water you're drinking delicious it is i buy these uh
i like
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): these a lot um i'll admit
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): I'll
Speaker 457: see
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): you
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): next time.
I had
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): a weird dizzy spell right before I went on air, like 10 minutes before I went on air. Super dizzy,
Speaker 457: sick to my stomach and room spinning. And
I almost thought I was going
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): to have to call the show off.
I let it go
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): for a minute. I get
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): migraines sometimes, and I
get a
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): little dizzy. I don't get the headache pain, but I get the visual auras, and a lot of times they're preceded by dizziness. So I thought I might be having a migraine. Yeah.
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): I did a workout today that involved 150 sit-ups. And while I was doing those, I got a little dizzy. So I don't know if I've got like a little
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): head cold blooming.
Maybe I thought
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): I might be a little dehydrated. So
I went
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): and grabbed one of these out of the fridge. And I figured I'd drink the whole 33.8 ounces while I was on air. And of
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): course, that leads to a dire need to end the
Speaker 187: program at some point and
make an
Speaker 187: emergency run to the bathroom. Not old baron. I feel great now, though.
Speaker 187: Not old, Baron. I think they mean wise
and a
Speaker 187: father people can look up to. No, but call no man father. I'm just kidding.
I would pick
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): that fight. I'm almost 60 and had a dreadful father, so I understand what a great dad looks like.
Speaker 248: Oh, I'm sorry to hear that, dear.
Sorry to hear
Speaker 458: that. That's a tragic story.
But thank you for
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): the kind words. Remember one month, keep up the great work,
and we get
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): Charlie's travel schedule for this year. Go Max, Christ is king, great fine Daisy.
We
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): probably could piece together where he was. I've been trying to do that a little bit.
Sir
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): Barron,
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): check out Trump's new Board of Peace charter signed at Davos. Makes DJT sort of a dictator. Thanks to expose this. Jesus is king. I will check it out. I'll check it out. Is it possible to find out if JE stayed in the same hotels as EK?
Speaker 254: Well, I don't know. We'll certainly try
to
Speaker 116: find the answer. I'm waiting for Trump to wear a tiny hat. I think he already has. Isn't there a picture of him at the wall with one on?
Daisy worked for
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): Turning Point. Not that Daisy. Different Daisy.
Speaker 75: well, you did say eight-hour... I think that daisy still works at Turning Point. Well, you did say eight-hour megastream
Speaker 195: at 1 million followers. That is true. Maybe I could do a... If I get to a million followers, I'll do a mega recap, whatever we've worked on to that point. That's a good call. Roll that beautiful. Man, that's going to be a long day. Y'all are going to
have to
Speaker 195: give me some breaks. Like, I'm going to take
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): it... It's going to be like OSHA or EEOC. I get 10 minutes every two hours or something, whatever the federal law is.
Speaker 181 (lower-pitched voice): Hey, Barron, good.
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): Google an ideal day, according to Erica Fransfain. Click
on the
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): Arizona Foothills Magazine link. This was when she was dating JT. I've read that article. What
am I
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): supposed to be seeing
Speaker 111: in it?
I did read
Speaker 459: that article.
Bro, this EK scheming
Speaker 307: against yay screams honeypot.
Speaker 250: Maybe.
Speaker 250: Brandon Tatum, graduate, University of Arizona, Tucson, PD, TPSA event speaker 2017 and 18,
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): takes job with TPSA very early 2018. It's possible CK was at the wedding. That's what I'm trying to find out. See if I got my source texted
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): back. Oh, did not, did not. AIBB said the belief out loud that the justification for people in Israel to abuse Christians, they closed the Holy Sepulchre in Jerusalem, closed for Lent Easter, similar to COVID time. Oh, AIBB?
The
Speaker 365: rumor around TPSA water
Speaker 460: coolers that Mark Levin is the tiny horse.
The tiny horse that Ben rides? Mark Levin. Everybody loves Mark Levin. Actually,
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): nobody does. Nobody watches that. Could some seminary professors be planted to Zionists to influence evangelical professors? Yes, they absolutely could. Infiltrated.
they
Speaker 187: need to hose the place down man have you heard about the horrible fires in nebraska i think fires are sus cattle country
no
Speaker 236: meat for
you christ is
Speaker 236: king i have not
Speaker 369: heard about them um let
me look
Speaker 369: fires nebraska oh
i've not
Speaker 170: seen
you
Speaker 170: remember when all those cows started dying a few years ago and then all the chickens died and like they were going and then the fertilizer plants exploded. You remember that?
That was
Speaker 463: weird. I don't
think that was
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): an accident. Western Area Power Admin has a facility in Watertown, South Dakota related to EMP research. I doubt it. I doubt it.
Joe Kent and
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): Tucker are so phony. They both know exactly what happened to Charlie. I don't know.
Kent
Speaker 305: France-Vey
Speaker 277: is an AZDEQ Copper World Op Report. Really? Was she traveling with her dad to Santiago, Chile?
Because there was the copper thing there. Just saw a post
Speaker 464: about an emergency flight from
Speaker 429: Telnof to Germany.
Can we
Speaker 429: check flight logs to see
Speaker 226 (lower-pitched voice): if there were any emergency flights if BB is alive?
Do we have a
Speaker 226 (lower-pitched voice): date? Do we have a time? I'm
sure that's
Speaker 226 (lower-pitched voice): not the only flight.
Is it
Speaker 444 (lower-pitched voice): just me or our weirdos in chat tonight? Well, I mean, we don't
use the W
Speaker 444 (lower-pitched voice): word, all right? Have some respect for your fellow chatters.
Are they weird? Just
Speaker 250: after I, the first part of BB's clip was a Will Durant long quote about Jesus and James' con, the story of civilization. He was agreeing, though. Well, yeah, he was. And I believe DJT was meant...
God
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): will decide if he goes to heaven, not him. I do feel he is a good man, but not always able to escape the least. His quote was, I don't feel like I'm going to heaven.
Like that. I'll see if I can pull the exact
Speaker 465: quote. I
don't think there's anything going to
Speaker 372: get me to heaven.
I'm
Speaker 372: not sure I'm going to be able to make it to heaven. That's not leaving a lot of room there. The French word attack
Speaker 466: in Paris claimed by ISIS, 4-23-2017. First
round of
Speaker 466: presidential election, Macron versus Le Pen. Oh,
that was on 4-20. Oh, I think she was
Speaker 467: there for
one of those two
Speaker 365: events.
baron did
Speaker 365: you get the pen organizer i made for you i sent it we too i did i had no idea who to who to thank i
Speaker 177: did get it thank you thank you thank you thank you it's in our kitchen in our kitchen so thank you for that uh
i
Speaker 468: appreciate that i'm glad i
Speaker 177: had an opportunity to thank you
i never know how
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): to thank people you
know uh the strikes
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): me as manufactured plausible deniability for time she needed to cover for secret activity um yeah
i mean it could have been planned i could
Speaker 187: have been but i mean again
and
you would
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): have to count on daisies six years later to find it or 10, eight years, however long later to find it. Uh, Andrew cluster in 2019 tweeted, Britney
Speaker 170: Spears is more important than anyone realizes protector. She's going to red pill.
Everyone fears ties
Speaker 170: into all this. I have it all. Also. Have you ever dived into Q either? Um, I have,
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): uh, died into, dived into cube pretty, you know, I looked at it. Uh,
uh,
you
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): have it all okay i got it i never thought britney spears was going to be the linchpin but i'm willing to hear it
Speaker 164 (lower-pitched voice): out hope to see mark's plane on the members live next friday i'm
excited i've
Speaker 469: already booked
it already booked
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): it next friday uh not this coming friday he had plans this friday i intended to do it tomorrow uh but eight days from now mark's plane will be on i
am so
Speaker 170: excited about that wasn't she sharing the one bedroom with that girl in nyc not nicole wash Ave one bed.
Speaker 170: I
Speaker 169 (lower-pitched voice): think
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): that was a one-bed, actually. I think TravisXNelioX on Twitter put that together. I've
been reading about Jones
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): and Colts for years. It's crazy what he
got
Speaker 250: away with, even before got in. I never heard about his link to intelligence until tonight. Makes sense. Thanks for all you do. That's
why you tune in. Learn new
Speaker 195: things every night, guys. I think what
people are
Speaker 195: trying to say is
she uploaded stock
Speaker 195: photos to
make it
Speaker 195: look like
she took
Speaker 195: herself. Oh, that could be.
Speaker 62 (lower-pitched voice): creeps go to sports to find victims. Is E.K. a creep? That's the significance of travel. But do we have any
Speaker 170: evidence she was there for sports? That's what I'm not making a connection. Someone spell it out for me. I'm missing. I can see it now. Adfleet. Baron
Speaker 207: with a French hat and a black and white horizontal striped shirt. As an Italian chef with Joe Sasto
mustache. As
Speaker 207: an Andes native in a poncho. Pleased and thank you.
That's a
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): lot of Baron.
I'll
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): bet Allie Beth is still stucky to BB. Yeah, yeah,
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): I agree. She probably is. I'm
not a
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): big fan of hers. There's no email link on your YouTube about Tab. Is it possible to see metadata on EK Travel Picks? Blessing? I don't
know the
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): answer to that. I think there's an
email address on it. Go to
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): YouTube. Go to my channel.
Go to
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): more. Yep, right there. More
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): info. View email address. I
don't know
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): any other way to...
Put it
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): out there. They won't let you do it uncovered, I don't think. It's there. Click more when
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): you go to my page.
Go to my
Speaker 470: channel. If
you type
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): this letter and numbers in the search engine in a straight line, no dashes,
Speaker 18: it's an Epstein file. I saw that, but I saw the Epstein file. I
have no
Speaker 18: idea what it means. Tell me what it means. Tell me what it says. Don't make me go on a scavenger hunt.
Get right to the point. Bishop
Speaker 3: Marmari Emanuel said Trump must acknowledge Jesus by name after he was elected. Christ is king.
I
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): believe you,
but I
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): don't know that he has. Super late. Just heard your opening statement. Didn't mention Ukiah, California. My dad went to school with his kids. He remembers riding his
bike to
Speaker 282 (lower-pitched voice): their house to ask the boys to come outside and play. I left a lot out, Misty, a lot. Because A, some of it was kind of irrelevant to the
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): point I was trying to make. And some of it didn't have the oomph I was looking for in terms of factual basis.
Have I
Speaker 195: researched how long CK, New Cabot, and how they met? No, I even asked that question tonight, how they met. Oh, my goodness, yes. I bet she's right, and they. Hi,
Speaker 18: B-B-Baron. Hey, if it's not Charlie's writing in the night before letter Erica posted, isn't that pause to legally
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): investigate, submitting a false document? May God be with you. I don't know who she submitted a false document to. I mean, you can't investigate somebody for an internet meme. Sir
Knight
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): Barron. Oh, I'm
back to being a
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): knight.
I am
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): late tonight. I just finished your part about BB Powerful Show. You're so right. Thanks for another powerful. God bless you and the fam. Well, thanks for joining us.
Can this
Speaker 250: high IQ outfit get a five-star review from EK? What more does it take? People watching? I
don't know how to get a
Speaker 471: five-star review. EK. How
do I
Speaker 169 (lower-pitched voice): like while watching on YouTube? Technology Challenge Maria here. Like and subscribe, everyone. I don't know. Someone
Speaker 250: explained it one night in the chat, and I don't remember how to do it. Gifted 10 subs. Wow. You
guys
Speaker 61: are going to be in for a fun one tomorrow.
How
Speaker 61: do I like? Oh, I just read that
one. I
Speaker 195: mean, she is following recruiting at sporting events. Do they match dates of travel? I cry every time you say Jesus loves you. Well, first,
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): thank
you for
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): that. I don't know about any sporting events. That's what I'm saying.
If
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): you have sporting events that were taking place and say, hey, here's a giant event.
That might
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): help, but I don't know of any. More gifted subs. Thank you.
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): Christ rose
Speaker 236: on day three, resurrection from death. Jesus is omnipotent, the most high. Jesus Christ, the one true king. Jesus overcame the grave, staying on our place as a sacrifice. Jesus loves us.
All
Speaker 222: right. I'd like to hear
Bibi say
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): all that. Misread, I guess. Truth or dare like kids game, not hunger game. Oh, yeah, yeah. We don't want citizens harmed. I
don't know that I
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): want to watch them play truth or dare. They're kind of satanic, you know? Who knows what
the
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): dares are going to be?
ELN
Speaker 235 (lower-pitched voice): likely attempted to provide legitimacy for EK recruiting
Speaker 407: people for modeling jobs in 2017. According to State Department, Santiago is a prime city for activities like this in 2017.
Well, that's
Speaker 228: interesting. Italy
Speaker 472: shows up in J-Mail, too? No. No. Italy, 2017.
Yeah, it
Speaker 474: does. April. We're
going to have
Speaker 309 (lower-pitched voice): to run this down. It might be a follow-up show on this if it all pans out. Our
Speaker 203 (lower-pitched voice): country's at grave risk. SBB wants to be a superpower in the Middle East and in the West. And pieces are in place to get it done.
I don't
Speaker 475: doubt that. I
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): don't doubt that he wants to be. If EK is what CIA operatives look like today, is it bad to feel unimpressed? Saw
a chat
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): mentioning they
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): did eat CK.
What? He was unalived in the
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): center of a penta. It would be a sacrifice. Candace realizes all connected concerning the
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): satanic elites. EK appears to be another connection, possibly. I don't.
I
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): wouldn't base
Speaker 226 (lower-pitched voice): it off of an
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): Instagram post or tweet or something. That needs real evidence. I don't
know how the
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): double chat happens. I don't either.
BJT expressing
Speaker 101 (lower-pitched voice): humility, deep shame for a woman.
But there's a way to
Speaker 149: get in.
Just
Speaker 476: say, convert, brother. Come
to the light. Take his
Speaker 305: hand.
I
Speaker 305: feel PDGJT knew beforehand Charlie Kirk had to go. Her BBN decision
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): might mean why the no access to heaven comment.
Well, that
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): would certainly keep you out. If you're killing people, you'd have to repent. Watch video and question. DJT being humble on heaven.
I've watched
Speaker 167 (lower-pitched voice): the
Speaker 170: video. The man said he's
not going
Speaker 170: to heaven. He doesn't think there's anything they can get him in. That scares me. That the man like that
Speaker 99: rules our
Speaker 170: country. It just
scares me.
I'm still
Speaker 99: waiting to hear him say Jesus.
The likes
Speaker 99: are on fire tonight. Great job, everyone. They are on fire. Wow. I'm
not sure what's gotten
Speaker 381: into you people, but thank you. Thank you. That's amazing. And
I did it for
Speaker 381: the third time. LOL. Sad
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): I'm going to give CK's show a watch tomorrow just to see the mention Daisy.
Yeah, I
Speaker 184: am too. I'm going to go to that 27-minute mark or whatever it was.
Speaker 184: Um, I think I got all you people over on the, on the, uh, grumbler side. One more
rabbi
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): Coleman. Don't
mean to
Speaker 168 (lower-pitched voice): frighten y'all, but the synagogue of the fallen is coming after us next. We are technically the new empire of Rome. I
hope
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): not.
Speaker 477: Gosh, I hope not.
Speaker 49: Guys, this has been fun. I enjoyed the early show. It's only 8.22. Get to have your evening back. Have your evening back. Or you on the other side of the pond. Have the rest of your day. I hope you guys enjoy it. It's been
Speaker 195: fun. It's been real. It's been real fun. And I'll be back tomorrow for a member show.
Not
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): sure exactly what time. Probably early afternoon.
I had
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): to guess. Could be as late as maybe 2 o'clock.
But I
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): like to try to do member shows a little earlier, like 1 or 1.30.
In the
Speaker 153 (lower-pitched voice): meantime, like,
subscribe, click
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): the notification on your way out.
Share with
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): the buddy. Helps the channel. And if you...
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): Ever think to forget,
even
Speaker 138 (lower-pitched voice): DJT, even the Beamster, because
he loves everyone. Jesus loves
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): you. Thanks, guys. Have a wonderful night,
and I look forward
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): to seeing you back soon. I'll be back for a regular show Sunday night.
Yeah, Sunday night. Member
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): show tomorrow, regular show Sunday night.
Have a
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): good night, everybody.